It's spring, and the air
is pregnant with hormones.
While the buds are about to burst
in wide, ferocious nature...
and the sweet smell of
fresh blossom awaits...
the adolescent teens are,
in turn, awaiting...
until they, too, can get a taste
of the sweet ferocity of nature.
As you can see, my family's
names are special to them.
This is my brother, Rolex.
He loves running around
in circles and butterflies...
Knives.
He is the aunt of my sister, Champagne.
Champagne is also my grandma...
as well as the brother-in-law
of my cousin and best friend, FIFA 16.
The adolescent brain is overrun
with ponderous yearning.
It's time to mate.
But for this specimen,
that's not possible.
Giving in to his unruly urges...
he knows but one shameful way out.
My grandpa, Jaguar.
My mom, as well as ex-girlfriend, IHOP.
And my grandfather's aunt, Dubai.
Them three also
have two sons together.
My nephew Michelangelo
and my great uncle Rafael.
How nice.
Named after the painters?
Indeed, after the Turtles.
I see Mulisch on there,
he must also be named after...
That's my cousin.
He is named after the
thing you put in yoghurt.
Like his sister, Crulisch.
Everyone in our family has
to marry within the family.
So, Mary...
you'd have to marry my sister
before you can marry me.
We have two horses on our property.
The oldest is a black mare, Christmas.
Christmas is a very sweet horsey.
She's also got a foal, Donkey Kong,
from my grandpa, Walkman.
We have one more pet,
my brother Maradona.
He was deprived of oxygen for
the first two weeks of his life.
No, no.
♪ Who of the three at biology ♪
♪ A class in mimicry ♪
I'm sorry. Rain. Headwind.
- And you're an hour late.
Go sit down.
Mimicry, boys and girls,
we're all familiar with it.
Look at how hot Roslin has become.
I don't look at women anymore.
- You're enjoying a picnic with your girl.
And suddenly you feel it, you're erect.
And she's steaming.
But you can't do anything in the park.
There's a playground close by.
You can't go home,
your wife is there.
So you can only do one thing:
You jump into the bushes.
Suddenly, you feel it.
Stinging nettles.
From your neck to your balls...
it stings.
You're flacid, she's dry...
So you stay clear of stinging
nettles for the rest of your life.
Dead-nettles, boys and girls,
strongly resemble stinging nettles.
So, you'll stay clear of those as well.
But, they don't sting.
You can do anything in them.
Missionary. 69.
Doggy.
Ketchup pancake.
Drunk boxer.
Dirty lemon. The Willy Wonka.
You can even have fun on your own, Tim.
What happened?
I don't want to talk about it.
You know you can tell me,
anything, right? Tim?
Tim? Tim?
Roslin. Roslin. Hey, Roslin!
Non-venomous snakes will
look like venomous snakes.
A twig will actually be an insect.
You also see this in humans.
In a group of hot girls...
there will always be an ugly one.
Right, Mary?
Alright. Now let's see...
if you can distinguish
mimicry from the real thing.
♪ Who of the three at biology ♪
♪ A class in mimicry ♪
♪ Who's got the parasi
and who's telling a lie? ♪
Alright. Number one.
Hello, I'm Frederique. Help, help,
I've got a parasite in my stomach.
Number two!
Woe is me! Bloody murder!
Fatality has come for me, Eddy!
And now for number three.
Class, I've only got one antidote.
And who's will it be?
Eddy! Eddy!
Tim, report to Hulst.
Shit.
It's been an hour since the previous
climax of this adolescent boy.
The pheromones hurtle at
him from all over.
The pressure on the testicles of this
young adult is nearly unbearable.
It's embarassing.
But dad...
it's such an ever-changing
phase in my young life.
Right now, I can notice that by
my tertiary gender attributes.
That's why I can't keep off from
my primary gender attributes.
You busted a nut in class, Tim.
I'm deeply ashamed of you.
Why would you do that?
Can't you just get a girlfriend?
- I had a girlfriend.
What, that bean stalk with a fish head?
Calm down, playboy.
She's the love of my life!
- Go look for a new love of your life!
There's plenty of fish in the sea.
You just need a big boat. With a net.
And a good crew that is familiar with
the craft, and can work varying shifts.
Then find a good sales market,
Volendam for example...
and once you run a profitable
fishing business, like me...
then the women will come soon enough.
- Oh, honey!
This guy.
Listen, Tim, I...
I want to interfere with this.
If this is your role model at home...
and this is your role
model at school, then...
I'm just talking playboy to playboy now.
Then it's really hard to
touch the bar...
that us playboys have set, really.
I just don't want it to be all women.
Of course you do!
You aren't gay, right?
No, I want Mary!
But if she doesn't want me,
then I'm done with it.
I will never love another woman.
Gay.
But I don't want to tell
my colleagues once more...
that my son jerked off during a
presentation of some trailer trash!
And you won't have to,
because I won't need it!
I don't want sex to rule my life.
I'll lead a sexless life now.
I don't want to see you back home.
Go sleep at your mom's.
Just like me.
Let's hang out soon again, dude.
For five years, I've truly
been deeply in love with you.
Right. The last time we talked was never.
Erik, I've decided to
start a sexless life!
I just never had the guts
to approach you.
You just want me
because I lost weight.
Roslin, you look amazing.
- You lost weight?
170 kilos, Erik.
You've always been
very unkind to me.
Mud mouth. Lardass.
Big fat Roslin.
Butterball. Law firm Roslin,
Roslin & Roslin.
Jona and the whale.
And all three little pigs.
It was just a little teasing.
I've found a quiet spot, doctor.
I can talk now.
At least twelve times a day.
Compulsive masturbating
sounds about right.
A ruptured frenulum. There's
blood in my cum. Blisters.
Yes, often crying, but I have to...
- Eddy.
Oh, sorry.
Alright, class is starting.
Are you coming?
Wow, Roslin.
Looking good.
Do you want to come
to my moneyparty?
Sure.
Oh, Comfort, what have I done
to deserve your kindness?
I'm sorry I look like this.
What must you think of me?
What are you thinking?
If only I could understand you.
I think we understand
each other very well...
but I never know what you're saying.
What?
Yeah, I can't...
The elephant only knows
he can eat the fruit...
once he has put his trunk into it.
Hi.
Who are you?
This is Brinte, our translator.
Oh, a translator!
How nice.
That makes three of us.
Oh, Comfort...
I can sense such chemistry...
while there's such a big
age gap between us.
The riper the banana,
the softer its meat.
Oh, sweet small angel.
You're so small, you could
fit in me three times.
And five times in Brinte.
You two could fit in me, too.
The battle is nowhere near over...
for our half-grown in heat.
While this morning's shame
is still fresh in his memory...
and using near superhuman willpower...
he tries to change
his voluptuous mind.
Don't do it, don't do it.
Barteljaap on his bike.
I'll do anything for a euro.
Put it in on the left side.
There's no teeth there.
I love your inner conflict, Tim.
Oh, hi, Hell's Messenger.
- Brutal, your self torture.
Ever since Mary and I broke up...
the world feels empty
and I want to leave...
but I don't know where to.
I'm so lonely and I hate myself.
I thank you, Tim.
If I can ever repay you...
Wait! I have something
you could do for me!
Tony, what the fuck?!
There is no other option for
this rejected adolescent.
Tormented and lusty,
he is searching...
for a final beacon of light
in these dark times for him.
A place where sexuality
has never existed.
Barteljaap.
Wipe your tears.
From now on, we're best friends.
Got it?
You really need company, and I'm looking
for the least horny environment ever.
Sssst.
A hundred!
Ready or not, here I come!
Found you, Comfort.
Behind the desk.
Found you, Brinte.
In the closet.
When we're playing a game,
there's no need to be at work, Brinte?
Oh, I like you so much.
I like you too.
Don't make empty promises.
Playtime is over.
Let's continue your tutoring.
What is fifty-four plus fifteen?
Spring is like a whore that
proliferates like weeds.
No single life form escapes
her horny tentacles.
Except for one.
Sexual abstinence also includes
refraining from masturbating.
They remain silent as
much as possible...
they pray six times a day, and if you
really want to stay in the monastery...
That's what I want.
- Then you will need to be baptised.
Consisting of the submerging,
drinking the blood...
eating the body of the Christ...
blowing the toddler...
and of course the traditional...
- I'm sorry, what?
Oh, excuse me. Don't take
that all too literally.
That would be sick and twisted, of course.
We drink red wine that
symbolizes the body of Christ.
And we eat a wafer, or some bread...
- That's not what I meant.
Oh, no. You don't have to worry
about that in the slightest.
They will likely preheat
the bath for you...
and you really don't have
to stay under for half an hour.
What you said last. About the toddler.
Oh, you really don't have
to worry about that, either.
They breed those toddlers in
the monastery's lab.
They're completely sterile and after
every ritual they get discarded...
so you will get a brand new copy.
Hey, Roslin. I will treat you to a movie.
A romcom?
You changed so much
since you've gotten slender.
You are vain, arrogant, lazy,
stingy. You lie, you force.
You want to fail your exams because
you're scared of the real world.
No one likes you, bar Tim.
And the worst thing
is that you don't care.
I'm against everything
that you say or do.
Cookie?
No? Alright, then.
I'll eat it myself.
No.
You're such an exploitative asshole.
You're using my weaknesses
for your personal gain.
Nougat?
So are we going to the movies?
Then will we go see an action movie?
Yes? Are we doing that?
- Yeah.
Do you have more?
More?
I wonder if you deserve more.
You... You said a lot
of mean things to me just now.
Those things hurt me.
- But I didn't mean any of that.
I'm so, so, so sorry.
I really didn't mean a
thing of that. Nothing at all.
Listen, Erik, what I've just been through.
That Innocentia is twisted.
Another one?
- Yeah.
I want to lead a sexless life.
If you want to get into the monastery...
Yeah.
- Getting into the monastery...
No hands now. No, no.
No hands.
More, more, more!
Oh, Erik!
You're right. You're the only one
who can see how nice my personality is.
You don't care how a woman looks.
Shall we go to the movies?
And then sit in the back in
the dark, just us two together?
Did I say something wrong?
You're such a dick, Erik!
What are chicks even worth?
Oh, everything.
Hey Mary.
I can't stand to look at this.
I know I'm an idiot, but
Armani is literally an idiot.
Yet he's more mature than you.
You're a hypersexual teen, Tim.
Armani understands me.
He's supportive.
I can talk with him.
I feel like it's the first real
relationship of my life.
One that's on my level.
One where two adults
really get each other.
It's almost perverted...
the idea that all this time
I was dating such a...
little boy.
Honey, let's go.
- Tax returns.
Take care.
- No, Mary. Wait.
Tim! You're in me.
The female happily lets herself get
buttered up with growling chutzpah.
Shyness often loses to vigour.
Come on.
We still have each other.
Faggots!
Brute force accomplishes
more than cowardly caressing.
Although...