In the Amazon this plant was used
by medicine men for mystical rituals...
but now the substance from this
plant is spread around the world...
and is present in all
hallucinogenic drugs.
Those drugs are dangerous.
People lose their identity.
They no longer know who,
what or where they are.
They become delusional. In short,
to show how dangerous this is...
I will test this drug myself today...
on Barteljaap.
Yes I will.
Open your mouth. Very well.
Really, if they hear my grades,
I can't go out anymore.
I'm not allowed to visit
you or Mary, no soccer.
Why do parents' evenings
happen so often?
There's so fucking many.
- For real.
Very good, just chew.
Am I still on time?
Yeah, he just
took it. Take a seat.
Ah, fun!
This is a nightmare.
Get me out. Get me out of here!
I am so lonely.
I hate myself!
What a wonderful
profession we have , eh?
My, my! Guys, don't
tell this to your parents.
That's what I want to do tonight.
Erm... Mr. Heydrich?
Would you uh...
Please tell our parents
during the meetings tonight that...
we will be alright
for English and Dutch...
and that you are pretty sure...
that we will make it through the year,
bitte, sehr?
Ja, I can say that.
Okay.
And I'm also going to say that you
keep French kissing each other.
But, but...
we don't do that at all.
I know that,
but I'm going to say it.
Und I will also say
that you peep...
whenever the first year boys
are changing clothes.
But we've never done that before.
- But that is what I'm going to say.
I will also say that you jerk
each other off in my class.
Und that you send
nudes to the other boys.
Basically, that you are
two dirty perverts.
Damnit.
Unless you show pippi.
What?
Show pippi in front of the
whole class. I heard it's special.
Yeah, uh... Yeah, it's okay.
It's great.
- Thank you.
Don't mention it.
- But I'm not showing it now am I?
Tiny Schmutzbuckel.
Pippi, show it.
Jetzt.
Come on, show it.
Pay attention.
[Singing the German lyrics to Pippi Longstocking]
Zwei mahl Drei macht Vier, widdewiddewitt
und Drei macht Neune
Ich mach' mir die Welt,
widdewidde wie sie mir gefällt
Hey Pippi Langstrumpf,
trallari trallahey trallahoppsasa
Hey, Pippi Langstrumpf,
die macht, was ihr gefällt.
Sehr gut!
That's enough.
I won't tell your parents anything.
- Yes!
But I will tell yours.
And also about your grades.
Fuck!
And that's why I like
being with your mother
I take her, I fuck her, I do her
I fuck her in the hole from
which a baby comes out
which a fart comes out
Dad. Mom.
I need to tell you something.
It's been going on for a while...
And that's also why things
are going so badly at school.
I'm gay.
Yeah, yeah, I think that's
pretty good already.
Couple of things.
You can be much more dramatic.
Don't be afraid of the silences.
It has to be more gay
or they will never believe it.
Fucking hell,
that it had to come to this.
It's a win-win, Tim.
Your parents won't be
angry at you...
and you're ruining
Heydrich's plan.
Love the look, Tim.
Erik, seriously. Pippi?
Fuck you, Ronnie.
- I'm going to savour this.
Lars' parents may come in.
Oh, oopsie. Wrong classroom.
Lars's parents.
That's us.
No, Lars.
- So this is what Lars was talking about.
We are Lars's parents.
No.
Lars.
- Indeed.
That Lars.
Excuse me?
Could we talk about Lars now?
You are both...
At least...
Yes, you are both...
Sir, can we please talk about Lars now?
Of course. Sorry,
how stupid of me.
Now I understand.
- What do you mean?
Well, you're putting it in the...
Right? And then the baby
also comes out of the...
Of course.
Shouldn't you just give Lars a wash?
All year round you give Armani
8. The whole year through!
I will give him an 8.
You give 8!
You give 8 all year round.
Yes...
The next parents may enter.
Hello dear boy.
- Mom and dad!
What are you doing here?
We heard that
it is parents' evening.
We reckoned:
We are parents too.
We're coming to
check on our son.
Come and give mom
and dad a hug, son.
Dad!
Oh, darling. You're getting
more handsome by the day.
Who is the strongest
boy in the whole world?
That's me, dad.
- Well done, son.
Here you go.
How are you doing, son?
I'm fine, Mom, but
I find it difficult here.
All beginnings
are difficult.
But you can do it, I
know that for sure.
That is also true.
But they bully me so much.
That's because they are
jealous of your golden heart.
Should your old man
have a talk with them?
What is it they do?
They throw food at me.
And they throw me around.
They hit me.
Sometimes they don't
even show up to class.
Today, they fed me
hallucinogenic drugs.
Oh, but that's it!
It's so strange: We've
been dead for years.
Mom...
Jesus. Soon the whole
school will think I'm gay.
Whatever, you still have Mary.
Hey guys.
Oh fuck, there they are.
Okay, wish me luck.
I'll see you on the other side.
Toi, toi, toi, darling.
Dad, Svetlana...
I have to tell you something.
It's been going on for a while.
It is also the reason why things
are not going so well at school.
Hey guys!
Cannon ball!
I am a...
Who is that? Do I know him?
That's our math teacher.
Why did he do that?
- He's on drugs, dad.
It's always something at the
parents' evenings. Is this what I pay for?
[speaking Polish]
We are leaving.
What did you want to say?
- Oh, nothing, nevermind.
What are you wearing?
- He forced me to.
Dirty junkies.
Do you see how dangerous it is?
I told him there's a pool here
and he jumps out the window.
That's why you never use
drugs like these.
And above all, don't let
yourself be forced to!
Let's go.
Have you tried bleach
yet? It's amazing.
Hey dude, you're covered
in blood. Here you go.
Yes, it's all gone now.
Whole year round he gives you 8.
Thanks, Dad.
Help! Help me!
Thank you.