WHAT UNFORTUNATELY DIDN'T
HAPPEN ON RUNDFUNK
You're Tim and Erik, right?
Yes.
I heard that you're
the coolest guys ever.
Yes.
- Yeah.
Wow.
Tim.
I never should've broken up.
Can we get back together?
Yes.
Amazing. This is my hottest friend.
I would love for you to touch her tits.
Alright.
Erik, go ahead as well.
I now realize that friendship
is more important than love.
OK, cool.
Here you go, Tim en Erik!
Pizza with pancakes and fries!
My mom doesn't allow
me to eat fast carbs.
Don't worry, it's okay!
Mom, what are you doing here? Go away!
Here you go, guys. Your homework.
You're amazing.
You may slap me.
Hey guys, this is 100 thousand
million euros...
for your amazing speech at
Mr. Heydrichs funeral.
Because, well,
he's dead.
I recognize so much of
myself in you, guys.
You simply got too much swag.
That's why you'll only get A's
the whole year round.
Here you go, your new schedule.
Wow, only sports.
Cool.
WHAT DID HAPPEN
ON RUNDFUNK
You suck!
The whole class failed the test.
Disgusting.
Goddamnit.
Are you mentally retarded, Tim?
Just going to give Lars a wash.
And this...
forget about it.
That's why we should fail this year.
r̶e̶c̶u̶m̶b̶e̶n̶t̶ bikes
faggot
Sorry, my bike...
rushing...
- Why do you have a bag?
School.
Are those books in your bag?
Yes.
We're failing this year, Timmy. Relax.
- Alright.
Here.
Why are you holding my hand?
- You wanted that.
I wanted to take your bag.
- How sweet.
You won't need that
for a while.
TEACHERS' LOUNGE
What is it?
I got a note saying there's
something in my inbox...
which is urgent and I had to come quick-
This is the teachers' lounge.
Yes.
- It's only for teachers.
But, I am a teacher.
Oh really?
I know all of the teachers,
but I don't know you, boy.
I'm Barteljaap, you
tripped me just last week.
I teach maths.
Oh really? You teach maths?
Then what is twenty thousand
four hundred eighty-nine...
times thirty thousand four
hundred fourty-five?
Well?
Six hundred twenty-three million seven hundred
eighty-seven thousand six hundred five.
Right?
Well, I don't know! I'm
not a maths teacher.
I'm a German teacher.
I can't check it.
Schade.
Could you please let me through?
How appalling.
A teacher would never beg,
a teacher would order.
Let me through. Now.
Go on.
A teacher can't order
another teacher.
You're doing that to me too.
Jetzt genügt es, ja? Danke.
Danke.
Tim, Erik...
once again you got
exactly zero books with you.
Well, we did have books in
my bag, but it's lost now.
Are you trying to fail this year?
You're aiming to fail?
Well... Yes.
Our grades are terrible, we'd need
to work too hard to graduate.
And this school is just too fucking
awesome. I get you. It's terrific, guys.
Did you guys know that this
is where a girl and I first...
Did you also attend this school?
- No way. Four years ago.
Cora, the coffee girl.
Her mom.
Since Papa is running the game here...
those women follow me
like a fly following shit.
By the way...
I kicked out Ms. Salt.
Art is sacred, but the things that
that chick was doing in class...
were simply dewomanizing.
I've hired Ms. Pepper, so she's new here.
She's a completely different character.
Alright, get your bag and go to class.
- But my bag is on the roof.
On the roof?
No one has ever left the roof alive.
Then you have to buy a
new set at the library.
We're so poor, mister Hulst.
And so tired too, mister Hulst.
We just want to relax.
Relaxing? Save that for
Barteljaap's class.
I have a better idea. Go see Tony.
He'll have a job for you.
We're not going to Tony, are we?
Fine.
You'll see me tomorrow
in your mother's kitchen...
baking an egg in my bare ass.
Tony?
Hey, guys. Could you spare me some money?
No.
- Nope.
Then could you spare me
some toilet paper?
Catch, Tony.
Wipe my ass.
I've had an accident, just
when it's my birthday.
Hey, guys.
You alright?
What can I do for you?
We're failing this year, so
we're not allowed into class.
I also failed a year once.
And look at me now.
Could you pass me
some clean pants?
We don't want to hold you
up on a beautiful day like this.
A very beautiful day.
It's my birthday.
Every day is your birthday,
isn't it, Tony?
So, we'll be on our way, then?
- So unfortunate.
Fuck.
- What?
It really is his birthday.
So what? We get to go home.
We can't leave him behind
like this, can we?
Look at him, on his birthday.
♪ Just three more years will Tony live...
said the doctor.
Just three...
- Tony.
Happy birthday.
We will make it a day to never forget.
Lars.
I'm sorry. About everything.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Only now I realize how stupid I was.
I made fun of you.
I called you a monkey.
I made fun of your gay parents.
I tried to wash you with bleach.
And no, I should never have
put you in the washing machine...
and certainly not the deep clean.
Those 2,5 hours could've killed you.
You do smell nice now.
Thanks.
I'm sorry, dear boy.
I can only imagine what you think of me.
It's OK, Viktor. Thank you.
Okay.
Here, some chicken.
O, sorry, wait.
Here, Kool-Aid.
I don't think you get it.
- I knew you were going to say that.
Look, shaved ice.
Okay, but...
trainers.
No?
No.
Lars, fist bump?
You can stop, Laquelle-Fer'Quengely.
He's stubborn.
Cheese sandwiches with
capers, dille and lemon.
Ham sandwiches with
It's for sharing, so it
needs to be bite-sized.
A cheese board with
capers, dille and lemon.
Sausages with
What about candy?
Licorice with
capers, dille and lemon.
Is there something without
capers, dille and lemon?
Absolutely. Salmon.
Let's take that.
Of course. That's €12,50.
Harakiri, give me some salmon.
All I have is five euros. You?
I have Thai money that look like
euro coins left over from a holiday.
Let's use that.
Can I keep one?
He, shit.
Harakiri, I asked for salmon,
but this is tuna.
Harakiri, no!
He, fuck.
Damnit.
It is salmon.
And... Heil Hi...
- Nein, nein, nein, kein Hitler!
I hate Hitler!
Ja, of course!
He killed Hitler!
Anyway.
Gut. Gut gemacht.
This technique is typical
abstract-expressionist.
I find it a lovely technique to use.
I can completely lose myself in it.
You can do it alone, but
it's is more fun to do...
when you're together
with your girl friends.
In stead of a lame high tea.
You can use thin brushes
for the details.
But it's super fun to mess
around with a thick one.
It is very important to effectively
use your pelvic floor muscles.
And if you do everything right, you
will feel an amazing cooperation...
between that brush and the ovaries.
Well then.
You all have your own brushes.
Samira, I've heard a
lot about your dad.
I got this one for you.
Hello, Miss Pepper, it's my birthday!
You're supposed to dip
the salmon in the custard...
then pinch your nose and swallow.
No, Mary can't have salmon.
She's allergic.
O, Timmy, I can't believe
you remembered.
Tony, keep off!
Tim and Erik want to join in.
Really? Guys, how fun!
What the fuck, Tony?!
It got uncomfortable.
Safe sex is important, guys.
Especially when doing
it with Toothless Tilly.
I'm done. We dump him.
- The fun is over.
No way!
You promised me!
Imma snitch, imma snitch.
Go on, Tony, get some more.
It's your birthday.
Just take it.
Take it, take it.
- Take it, Tony, take it.
Yes, yes, yes.
There we go.
Let's go.
- Yep.
Fuck!
We killed Tony.
- Now we need to give him CPR.
Not it!
No way, I'm not touching
Tony's disgusting mouth.
I can't. I have a girlfriend.
Fuck!
I had a girlfriend.
Hey, I was nearly dead.
Amazing birthday, guys.
Thank you so much.
You can go.
LOOK TO YOUR RIGHT
LOOK TO YOUR LEFT
ACTUALLY LOOK
TO YOUR RIGHT AGAIN
Hello Barteljaap.
As you know, I've been
sick at home all day.
That's why, unfortunately, I couldn't
show this new girl around at school.
Achoo!
Could you, bitte, take
over this task for me?
Ouch, ouch, my head hurts so much!
Thank you. Lieber Grüsschen
von Herr Heydrich.
Hi Tim, I'm Mary's dad.
You were a worthless son-in-law.
Hey, Timmy.
How was your day?
It was very nice of you to help Tony.
Anyhow, I, er...
I missed you.
I know that I called you
a toddler and all that...
But, er...
you're my toddler.
What I actually wanted to...
How did you get that cold sore?
You kissed someone else!
- I didn't!
Are you mimicing my dad?
- No, Mary, wait!
Look...
Today was the first day at school without
you, and it was the worst day ever.
Really.
Is that salmon on your hand?
Shit, I'm sorry.
Your allergies, I'm so sorry.
Hey, guys.
Wanna buy a bike?
Tony, what is this?
That's my bike.
No way, it's mine.
But for five euros, it's yours.
Five euros?
I don't have that. I spend it
all on your birthday treats.
What?
Five euros?
Here you go.
You like it like that, right?
I saw you in art class.
Yeah, they like that.
Tim?
Yeah?
Is this your backpack?
Yup.
Thank you, Eddy.
Hey guys.
This is Comfort. She's new here.
I'm showing her around.
Hi Comfort.
I don't think she speaks Dutch.
She's from Thailand.
For you.
Hey, Lars.
No Viktor, not now please.
Hold on, I think you'll like this.
- No, Viktor!
I'm done with you!
Get lost! That's enough!
Sorry Lars, about everything.
I feel you.
I feel...