OMINOUS MUSIC
One movement says more than 1000 words.
Hello?
SNORING
THREATENING MUSIC
WAAAAAAAAH! Aaaah!
Oh, crap. Oh, fuck. Oh, shit.
I won't lie,
of course I also
thought about it sometimes,
it was bound to happen.
You're young, good friends,
but you have to push that away
and then you don't think about it anymore.
Okay, nobody saw anything.
I won't tell anything.
We are just friends,
nothing happened.
Tim! It was dark and I stumbled
and I just fell on you.
That's what we're going to say: You stumbled
and you just fell. That's really true.
Really? Yes.
But I am glad you're here, I was
afraid I was locked up all alone.
I was afraid we were gay.
Where are we?
Barteljaap's classroom, 308.
Are we locked up? Correct.
Why?
Do you remember anything?
How did we get here?
Eh... I only know that I woke up
with my face on the table.
A fountain pen in my pocket.
Good idea, check your pockets.
Oooh...
Yes.
I remember it again, of course.
We had a social studies test
in this room, Barteljaap was proctoring.
Then there was a very difficult
question, I remember that.
Then I went to have a quick wank,
that always puts me in a nice haze.
And then I woke up here.
How long would we have slept?
Three hours?
Maximum 3.5.
Hey man, you have
ink all over your face.
Ugh, gross. Hey.
Come here.
Like this.
Whoops.
It's even near the corner of your mouth.
Yuck, take it away.
Like that, yes, yes.
Yes. Yes.
Good.
Thank you.
So 3 hours, 3.5 hours.
I feel my evening rumble coming,
it must be about 7 o'clock now.
I don't know. I had to hand in my phone
for the test. Me too.
Can't you call someone? No, I had to
hand in my phone for the test.
Ah, me too. Fuck!
My mother will be worried,
it's Friday night,
soon we'll be here all weekend,
we'll be dead!
We must have slept deeply
if nobody woke us up.
Or nobody tried to wake us up.
What do you mean? Think, Erik.
It is very coincidental that
the two of us are sitting here.
We are very special boys.
We are the heartbeat of the school,
we set the course.
This was a social studies test.
Haha, that test is far from finished,
why else would we be locked up here?
Well, that...
is because we fell asleep.
Oh, Erik.
The game has begun.
See? You can't fool me.
See? You can't fool me!
Check the desk for clues.
WOLF HOWLING Double full moon.
And?
Eh... nothing. Just a few sad things.
And a compass.
BANG
Tim? What was that?
It's locked.
Maybe it came from outside. BANG Waah!
Hello?
Maybe we shouldn't want
that cupboard to open.
Waaaah!!
Barteljaap!
Is he dead?
What is that smell? Corpse smell.
No, this is not a corpse, that's a doll.
How do you know?
That face is so poorly finished,
it looks terrible.
I know, lift his skirt.
Why? Dolls don't have a gender.
What is this?
This is Barteljaap's dick.
Isn't this Barteljaap's vagina?
No. Look here.
This is a ball, that's a ball.
He just has a kind of long sack.
Look, that little thing above it,
that's his dick.
I would swear this is roughly
what a vagina looks like.
Who here has had a girlfriend?
No, look...
Barteljaap has this. Yes?
A long sack...
dick. Yes?
It runs all the way to the bottom.
At the bottom is the anus.
A vagina is at the front,
it's very different.
Here the navel, under that
always a lot of...
pubic hair and at the front
is a very long slit.
That's the vagina. You rub there, after
a while you go to the bottom...
there's a little hole, that's the anus.
If that's wet, you're done.
Yes, now that you say it, I remember.
But then this is Barteljaap.
Yes.
That smell. Corpse smell, yes.
So he is dead then?
Holy shit!
Who is sick enough to think this up?
Heydrich.
If Heydrich is capable of murdering
Barteljaap, what will he do to us?
I have to go home, to my mother!
I don't want to die.
We have to be gone by 10 o'clock.
What time is it?
I had to hand in my phone
for the test.
We must act quickly. But don't
make any stupid, rash decisions.
We must cut open the corpse. What?
I know I'm not
your smartest friend
and I probably won't be either...
but if I'm an expert in ONE
field, it's the horror movie.
The key to the door is
in Barteljaap's stomach,
we cut him open and run outside.
Easy as that. Maybe you
find it a sick idea... Compass? Yes.
Good.
I had a push pin, but it was taken.
Okay.
Here we go.
1...
2...
I don't know how to do this.
Nobody knows, right?
Yes, Harakiri, but...
MOBILE PLAYS DEUTSCHLAND UBER ALLES
Hey, we can call.
A text from Heydrich. 10 more minutes.
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
What is Harakiri's number?
How should I know, 06-harakiri?
JAPANESE Hello?
Harakiri. Yes! Harakiri.
Hi, this is Tim and Erik.
I just have a quick question.
Is it possible to cut
a stomach open with a compass?
JAPANESE
Yes, it happened ONCE before.
You have to make sure you're exactly
two centimeters above... JAPANESE
Sorry, you said that last
word a bit unintelligibly.
That's not bad, can happen,
no, Harakiri no!
No, no, no! JAPANESE SHOUTS
We can call home! You do it.
Fuck, credit finished!
Fuuuuuck!!
NO SOUND AUDIBLE
I'm sorry, Erik. I thought I could save
us from this. It's okay.
Even if we die, at least I am with you.
I played the game but I lost.
18 springs young and already dead.
Maybe if I hadn't jumped to
such hasty conclusions. So young...
So not having lived.
It is only normal that you get to decide...
So many things not done.
I know nothing about the world.
You're my best friend.
I've never even been blown.
Tim, would you want to do that?
Fantastic.
I promise I won't groan, look or come...
but I just have to know how it feels.
Oooh.
Erik, I don't know if I can do this.
You're my best friend.
TIM LETS OUT A CRY OF HORROR
Everything for the friendship.
You're a dirty, rotten cheat, Erik!
That's very sweet...
but I don't really get turned on by
dirty talk. A secret correspondence with Eddy!
It's not what you think, Tim.
'Hi Erik, we are a good team.
Greetings, Eddy.' Listen now.
'Hi Eddy, we certainly are. Say
nothing to Tim. Greetings, Erik.'
'Hi Erik, I think I left my pinball
machine at your house.'
'PS. We are friends.'
At your house, Erik!
Do you know how often in
those six years
I have been invited to your house.
Not ONCE!
And Eddy... Eddy was, yeah.
Why? We do everything together!
Yes, everything!
And now that's suddenly not fun anymore?
Eddy at least doesn't hang on my neck
all the time.
I'm practically drowning because of you.
Erik, I have to poop, are you coming?
Erik, let's invent a toilet where
we can poop opposite each other!
Erik, can you take a photo of my poop?
Your camera is better!
Is there anything you can do without me?!
I am heart-broken and lonely
without Marietje right now!
Marietje! I was wondering when
you'd start on that broad.
Marietje also thinks you're a clingy
kid who doesn't want to learn. Dirty bastard!
GROWL
Tim!
Can you stay with it a bit?
I dreamed I was being
strangled by a zombie.
ECHOING: Tim! Tim!
Tim!!
Tim!
Erik!
Nobody strangles my best friend.
Tim! Wake up!
Hey Tim! Wake up please.
Hey! Are you okay?
Come on. TIM COUGHS
Thank you for saving my life.
I'm sorry I'm so dependent on you.
I'm sorry, Tim.
That I was secretly with Eddy at my place.
That I said you cling to me,
it's not like that.
I have a shitty house, Tim.
It's not like your house at my place.
Why do you think I fall
asleep at school.
I don't sleep a wink in that house.
And Eddy always has them closed.
He doesn't see that the fridge is empty.
The liquor cabinet full.
That...
doesn't see my mother's bruises,
my father's red nose.
I'm dead ashamed and I don't
want anyone to see me there.
And Eddy doesn't care about any of it.
I also don't care about any of it.
I'm just glad you're telling me honestly,
instead of always coming up with excuses.
'We can't be at my house because
the toilet is blocked.'
my house is out of the way.'
It's time.
That was it then.
Shall I blow you real quick?
No, that's fine.
Soon that door will fly open.
And then it's finished.
I love you.
I love you too.
So terribly much.
HEYDRICH: Surprise, surprise.
Finally!
It's been a tough time but everyone
gets what they deserve.
I have brought something for you,
completely for you alone.
The party can begin.
It's actually quite dark here,
don't you think? Oh, sorry.
Light on! Door shut!
Cool, right?
Hey, boys! Are you still here?
You had fallen asleep during the test.
And you were sleeping so nicely that
I didn't want to wake you up.
But at least you're well rested. Nein!
That's not the surprise!
There is someone here for you,
someone who is very dear to you.
Someone you lost,
someone who went missing
in the prime of her life.
Batskelien!
My identical twin sister! HEYDRICH LAUGHS
Did you find her? M-hm.
Really?!
I've been paying a detective for years...
90 percent of my salary to find her!
I know that, because that detective
is now her boyfriend...
and they travel all over the world...
looking for exclusive full moon parties.
And they also have a very nice blog,
here look.
Because when I told her there was also
an exclusive full moon party here...
she immediately flew over first class.
Jaha!
Great.
That...
That is my holiday.
Vacation.
Say...
Your little sister is in the cupboard.
Cupboard open!
Batskelien! No!
No!
Batskelien!
What did you do to her?
Now really, boys!
Why?!
Yes... Hello, eh...
Yes, eh... You had locked us in here
with the light off.
I didn't lock you in at all
with the light off!
Light on! Door open!
Yes, but we didn't know that.
And you opened that cupboard yourself.
Yes, Barteljaap, you opened the cupboard.
We thought we had ended up in
a horror show.
There's also a camera and everything.
I use that to film my lessons...
to find points for improvement
in myself.
If you had paid more money
to that detective...
she would have had credit.
Then we could have called for help.
I understand it looks very strange like this,
but she looked very dead...
and then she attacked me and started
strangling me.
Oops! That might be my mistake.
I threw the schnapps and the nice
party things
in the cupboard with the girl.
But your sister also has a very bad
reaction to drink, you know!
There was also a corpse smell and everything.
Those were my little farts.
I am very insecure about my bowel movements.
Annoying.
Anyway, luckily you had an ashtray
I could hit her with, because otherwise it
would have ended badly.
Ashtray?
No! No! Papa and mama!
HE CRIES
My whole family is lying here!
I love it when a plan works.
Sorry, what did you say? Nothing.
Sorry Barteljaap.
It was just an unfortunate misunderstanding.
Yes, can happen.
It's fine.
For too long I have let myself be
walked over
and let myself be used by everything
and everyone!
That is going to change from now on.
I may have lost my
identical twin sister...
but I am going to find myself!
I find it sad.
Barteljaap all alone.
GROAN
No, no, no!
Cancel 'Barteljaap all alone'!
Cancel, cancel!
If you don't say anything,
then eh... I won't say anything either.
Door open!
Sad Barteljaap, all alone.
MUSIC: BRIGHT EYES BY ART GARFUNKEL
♪Is it a kind of dream
♪Floating out on the tide
♪Following the river of death downstream
♪Oh, is it a dream?
♪There's a fog along the horizon...♪