Yes, yes. That's true, yes.
Yes.
That's right.
Oh yeah.
H-hm.
Yes.
But I'm going to hang up now,
because I can see you.
Yes, that's alright. Bye, bye.
Hey dude.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
- Eighteen.
Yeah dude, eighteen.
Finally grown up, finally legal.
I mean: Ms. Wevers,
Ms. Salt, Armani's mom...
they've always wanted me,
but now it's allowed.
Wow, cool.
What were you doing?
- Oh, look.
No, you shouldn't do that, dude.
- But he gets candy, right?
You should leave that first-year alone.
- I think he can handle it.
You have to leave him alone!
- Why?
Don't know who that is?
- No?
That's Red Ronnie.
- Who?
Red Ronnie.
Everything you give him
he'll shove up his ass.
Everything?
- Everything.
Dude, stop.
I'll hit you back.
- Do it.
Do it, I'll hit you back
three times as hard.
Of course.
I didn't even touch you!
You wanted to.
- You're so fucking stupid.
Really, am I stupid? Really?
Then who recieves the punches?
- Hey class, good morning.
Well, I do say good morning. But
actually something is bothering me.
I have graded your tests and
they haven't been done well.
I can only blame myself for that.
So I decided not to publish the grades.
Then we will discuss it today,
And you will get a
second chance next week.
I get that that's
not ideal for you either.
So I have made a delicious apple pie from
my mother's recipe. Pass it to the others.
Well, let's get to it.
Are there any questions?
Barteljaap.
- Erik. Happy birthday, by the way.
Yes, thank you.
What is it?
- At question 1,
I've got the X on one side and
the Y on the other side.
But what I don't understand is, um...
how long you've been gay for.
No, but I'm not, uh...
Sorry Barteljaap. That was stupid.
I do have a serious question. At 7A.
It says something
about linear growth.
I know about exponential
growth and all that, but why...
do you enjoy French
kissing with men so much?
Tim and Erik, don't
be so childish.
Sorry, Barteljaap.
I do have one question.
At page 3.
Um...
Because what do you like
most about having sex with men?
Haha yes.
Well, let's just start with question 1.
That seems best to me.
Your cake is gross!
Quit it!
Did you throw my notebook in the ditch?
You hit me all the time, all right?
This notebook had all my
homework. You're doing it.
You're doing my homework?
- Yes. Calm down.
At three o'clock, otherwise
you'll wake up dead tomorrow.
Guys, class isn't over yet.
Come on.
So my father has a
very good lawyer anyway.
He's going to put a stop to it anyway.
Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
Cookie gets really upset if
I have to sit there all day.
The humidity here is just
very different than it is at home.
He went to the hairdresser yesterday...
Ladies, pay attention for once!
Are you doing math right now?
You really don't have to do your
homework for Barteljaap.
You do homework for yourself,
not for someone else.
Ladies, if you don't pay
attention it won't work.
You did your test so well
yesterday and now this.
At three o'clock I'll be
free for half an hour,
so if you'll be ready, then...
Damnit!
Class has started.
Tim, please pick up that ball.
Frederique, be quiet.
What's going on?
So I took Cookie to school.
- Cookie?
We had to bring our pet for biology.
Mr. Heydrich saw it and said it wasn't allowed
and then he took him away.
Three o'clock!
So then I had to go to his
office and he has to sit there all day.
He put him in a very small dirty
hole with Jews and stuff.
I get the feeling that...
Very worrisome indeed,
but you have class now.
You'll probably get him back
this afternoon.
Alright, now for something else.
We'll be having a new student today: Lars.
Lars will come to class
soon. Be a little nice.
Show some understanding.
It's not easy for Lars.
A new school, strange people.
Oh, Frederique.
That's so cute.
You dressed him in clothes
and all. Hello, hello Cookie.
I thought you meant a pet
hamster or something.
That's not Cookie.
Well Goddamnit. Shoo!
Go away, hey!
Hey, Viktor.
That's Lars.
Hi.
Oh, sorry. I...
Apologies.
You are Lars, of course.
Sorry, everyone. I...
It's okay.
Hey, Lars.
Look.
Do you want, do you want to sling?
Viktor, stop it.
I need to stop?
- Yes.
What do you mean,
stop it?
You think he can't
do this? Animal hater!
You now he can sling from that rope,
to that basket and back again.
Disgusting!
I asked you to be a little
nice and understanding to Lars.
I'm not seeing any of that.
They've been to the moon, you know?
They have a higher IQ than some people.
Of course, just walk away.
Just because you can't handle it...
that you are not the only
living being on this planet.
Come on, Lars.
All right. The human body is one
of the most beautiful things to draw.
Ms Salt.
She treats me so differently
now that I'm 18, that horny bastard.
She doesn't want you, stop it.
- ...female body...
and the male body.
- You're just jealous.
For what?
That you don't have such a horny slut.
- Mary gives me plenty of handjobs.
For six years she has been
sowing, that dirty pencil box.
Now that I am legal,
she wants to harvest.
Guys, pay attention.
This is important material.
You want this in your repertoire.
- And what if I don't want that?
Then you can report to me and stay
in detention all afternoon.
Did you get that?
- You and I get each other very well.
Can I say Salty?
- No, but you can stay late.
I'm going to completely
soak her.
Dude, she doesn't want you.
Finished.
Okay, let's all pay attention. The balls.
Think an upside down
heart, but leave out the end...
and draw two smooth lines to the stem...
make sure there is a
nice transition here...
and I want to see firm round balls...
no tangerines in a net.
You draw the hairs by gradually
reducing the pressure on the brush.
So from rough to soft...
from rough to soft.
Personally, I prefer shaved balls...
but you don't put paper
with paint in your mouth...
so for once hairs won't hurt.
Well, that was my sample cock.
At the end of this week
I want your own cock...
in my mailbox, in my drawer.
I don't care how, but I want that dick.
When I say your own cock,
I really mean that.
There will be no copying, I know
your dicks from the first year camp.
Plagiarism is punished with an F.
You all have sheets and paint.
Lars, I'll give you a larger sheet.
And, Pong Feng, you can draw on this.
Then you also don't have
to color it in anymore.
But ma'am, we don't have a dick.
"But we don't have a dick."
Just draw your father's cock.
And if you don't remember
how that one looks like...
You can use the cock of
Samira's dad as reference.
Ma'am, do you have any large brushes left?
Where is my notebook?
Where the fuck is my notebook?
Ronnie!
Oh, sorry.
What's this about?
- Hey, Armani.
I'm not Armani, I'm Tim.
Oopsie.
Where the fuck is my homework?
All gone.
You're on thin ice, bud,
you better watch out.
Hmm, I can't wait.
Can't you be normal? Freak.
You have to help me.
If I don't finish Armani's homework
within thirty minutes, he'll kill me.
No way, I'm get to stay
late with Ms. Salt.
She doesn't want you.
Can't I have a bit of fun too?
You get spoiled by Mary.
If I don't finish that homework,
there will be no fun left.
Listen, fuck Ms. Salt.
- That's what I plan to do.
You have to help me, I beg you.
I beg you.
I think you're right.
Salt doesn't want me.
Correct, come on.
Dude.
Fuck.
Hey boy,
did you fall off your bike?
Fuck!
Tim.
Are our men running away again?
What a shame.
I would've completely drained Erik.