One move is worth a thousand words.
Hello?
Oh, crap. Oh, fuck. Oh, shit. Crap.
I'm not gonna lie, of course I thought
about it. It was bound to happen.
We're young, good friends, so you can confuse
it for love but you have to bottle it up.
No one saw anything.
I won't tell anyone.
We're just friends, nothing more.
Tim, Tim, Tim.
I couldn't see, so I
tripped and fell on you.
Great idea. You just
tripped and fell on me.
No, that's what actually happened.
Really?
- Yes.
I'm happy you're here, I was
afraid of being here all alone.
I was afraid we're gay.
Where are we?
Barteljaap's classroom, 308.
So we're trapped in here?
- Correct.
Why?
Do you remember anything?
How did we get here?
I only remember waking up
with my face on the desk...
There was a pen in my pocket.
- Great idea, check your pockets.
Yeah.
I remember. Of course.
We had a sociology exam in this classroom.
Barteljaap was proctor.
I remember that there
was a very difficult question.
Then I jerked off real quick,
because it gives me such a buzz.
Then I woke up here.
How long did we sleep for?
Three hours?
Maximum three and a half.
Dude, there's ink all over your face.
Ew, gross.
Come here.
It's even close to your mouth.
- How disgusting.
Yeah, that's it.
Very well.
Thanks.
- So it's been three and a half hours.
I feel my evening dump coming,
so it must be around 7.
I don't know. I had to
hand in my phone.
Me too. Can't we call someone?
No, I had to hand in my phone.
Ah, me too. Fuck!
My mom will get worried. What if we
can't leave all weekend and we die?
We must've had a deep sleep if
no one was able to wake us up.
Or no one tried to wake us up.
Whatcha mean?
- Think about it.
It's quite the coincidence
that it's us two here.
We're two very special guys.
We're the heartbeat of the school.
And we had a sociology test.
The test isn't over. Why else
do you think we're trapped?
We just slightly... dozed off.
Oh, Erik.
The game is afoot.
Don't you see?
You can't fool me.
You hear that?
You can't fool me!
Erik, search the desk for clues.
mom and dad
Double full moon.
And?
Nothing, just a few sad things,
and a compass.
Tim? What was that?
It's locked.
Maybe it came from outside.
Hello?
Maybe we don't want
the cupboard to open.
Barteljaap?
Did he die?
What's that smell?
Smells of a corpse.
No way, this...
This is not a corpse.
This is a doll.
How do you know?
Look at the finish on
that face. It's horrible.
I got it! Lift his skirt up.
- Why?
Dolls don't have genitals.
What's this?
This is Barteljaap's dick.
Isn't this his pussy?
No way. Look.
This is a testicle.
That's a testicle.
They're kind of...
Long nuts.
The thing on top is his dick.
I'd swear that this is
what a pussy looks like.
Who dated a girl for three years?
Look...
This is what Barteljaap has, right?
A long testicle...
and dick. Right?
It extends to the downside.
That's where the anus is.
A pussy is at the front.
It's different.
There's the belly button,
under that is a lot of...
pubes.
And at the front
there's a very large slit.
That's the pussy. That's what you rub.
Then you head downwards...
there's a hole there.
That's the anus.
And if it's wet, you're done.
When you put it like that,
it makes sense.
That would mean that this is Barteljaap.
Yeah.
That smell.
- Smells of a corpse.
So he's dead?
I'M GOING TO KILL YOU
Who'd be crazy enough to do this?
Heydrich.
If Heydrich killed Barteljaap,
what will he do to us?
I want to go home!
I don't want to die.
We need to be out by 10.
What time is it?
- I had to hand in my phone.
We need to act quick.
But we shouldn't make any
stupid, hasty decisions.
We need open the corpse.
- What?
I know I'm not your smartest
friend, and I know I'll never be...
but if there's one thing
I know, it's horror movies.
The key is in Barteljaap's stomach.
We need to cut it open
and make a run for it.
That's it. I know it's gross...
- Compass?
Yes, great.
I had a pricker, but it got confiscated.
Alright.
Here we go.
One...
Two...
I don't know what to do.
- Who does?
Harakiri does, but...
We can call.
A text from Heydrich.
Ten minutes left.
What's Harakiri's number?
I don't know, 06-HARAKIRI?
Hello?
Yes, Harakiri.
It's Tim and Erik.
We have a question.
Is it at all possible to cut open
a stomach with a compass?
Yes, it happened once in Ancient Japan.
You need to cut exactly
two centimeters above...
You said that last word
a little unintelligible.
That's okay, Harakiri.
Don't worry.
No, Harakiri, no!
We can call home!
- You do it.
Fuck, no credit!
I'm sorry, Erik.
I thought I could get us out.
- It's okay.
At least I've got you by my side.
I played the game, but I lost.
18 years young and already dead.
Maybe if I didn't make
such hasty conclusions...
So young...
No good life at all.
You should get to
decide our final moments.
Missed out on so much.
Didn't get to see the world.
- You're my best friend.
Never even got a blowjob.
- I'd do anything for you.
Tim, would you do that?
Amazing. I promise not
to moan, look or cum...
I just need to know what it feels like.
Erik, I'm not sure about this.
- You're my best friend, Tim.
Anything for friendship.
You're one nasty bastard, Erik!
That's very nice, but I
don't get off on dirty talk.
Secretly writing to Eddy?
It's not what it looks like.
'Hi Erik, we're a
great team. From Eddy.'
Please listen.
- 'Hi Eddy, we sure are...'
'Don't tell Tim. Cheers, Erik.'
'Hi Erik. I forgot my pinball
machine at your house.'
'Cheers, Eddy.
P.S. We're friends.'
At your house!
Do you know how often I've
been at your house? Not once!
And Eddy...
- Yes, Eddy has.
Why? We do everything together.
Yes, everything!
And now you don't want to?
At least Eddy doesn't
depend on me so much.
It feels like suffocation.
Erik, I need to shit, want to join?
Erik, let's invent a toilet such
that we can shit facing each other.
Erik, please take a picture of
my dump. Your camera is better.
Can you do anything without me?
I'm just so very sad and
lonely without Mary now!
Of course. I was wondering when
you would mention that hustler.
Mary also thinks you're a
clingy boy that can't learn.
You dirty bastard!
Are you staying with us?
I dreamt about getting
choked by a zombie.
Tim! Tim!
Tim!!
Tim!
Erik!
Nobody chokes my best friend.
Tim! Wake up!
Please wake up. Tim.
How are you?
Thank you for saving my life.
I'm sorry I'm so dependent on you.
No, I'm sorry, Tim.
About secretly inviting Eddy.
I said you were clingy,
but it's not like that.
My home is terrible, Tim.
It's certainly not like your home.
It's why I sleep at school.
I can't close my eyes at home.
Eddy always has them closed.
He can't see the empty fridge.
The packed liquor cabinet.
He...
He can't see my mom's bruises,
and my dad's beer bottles.
I'm ashamed and I don't
want anyone to see it.
And Eddy doesn't care.
You know I don't care, either.
I'm glad that you're honest about it,
instead of telling excuses all the time.
We can't go to my place,
because the toilet is clogged.
We can't go to me place,
because it's off route.
It's time.
That was it.
Do you want me to blow you?
- No, it's fine.
Soon the door will open.
And then it's over.
I love you.
- I love you too.
So very much.
Surprise, suprise.
Endlich.
It's been a rough time, but
everyone gets what they deserve.
I've got something for you.
For you, and you alone.
Let's get the party started.
It's a bit dark in here, don't you think?
Oh, sorry.
Lights!
Close door.
Cool, right?
Hey, guys.
Why are you still here?
You fell asleep during the test.
I'M GOING TO KILL YOU
You were so tired, so
I just let you sleep.
At least you're well rested now.
Nein, nein. That's not the Überraschung.
There is someone here for you.
Someone you're very fond of.
Someone you lost. Someone...
who went missing
in the prime of her life.
Batskelien!
My identical twin sister!
Did you find her?
Really?
For years, I've been paying a detective
90 percent of my salary to find her.
I know. That detective is
now her boyfriend...
and they've been travelling
all around the world...
looking for exclusive
full moon parties.
They also have a great blog.
Just look at this.
When I told her that there was a
exclusive full moon party here...
she immediately flew over in first class.
It's amazing.
That's my holiday.
Urlauben. Anyway...
Deine Schwesterche is in the cupboard.
Cupboard open.
Batskelien!
No!
What did you do to her?
Come on, you guys!
Why?
Well...
Come on.
Yeah, er... You locked us in
here with the lights off.
I didn't lock you in here
with the lights off at all!
Lights on!
Door open!
But we didn't know that.
And you opened the cupboard.
Yeah, Barteljaap.
You opened the cupboard.
We thought we were in a horror movie.
There's a camera and everything.
I use it to record my classes,
so I can look for what to improve.
Well, if you had paid that
detective a little more...
she would've had phone credit.
- We could've called someone.
I know it seems odd when
you look at it like that...
but she seemed dead and then
she started attacking me!
Oops! That might be my fehler.
I put the Schnaps and the party snacks
with das Mädchen in the cupboard.
But your sister gets a
really bad mean drunk!
It smelled like corpses in here, too.
- Sorry, those were my farts.
I'm insecure about my bowels.
Anyway, luckily you had an
ashtray I could smack her with...
or it might've ended badly.
Ash tray?
No. No!
Mom and dad!
My whole family lies on this floor.
Sorry, what did you say?
- Nichts.
I'm sorry, Barteljaap.
It was just an unfortunate
misunderstanding.
Those happen.
It's okay.
For too long I have let myself get
walked over and get used by everyone!
That all changes now.
I may have lost my
identical twin sister...
but I will refind myself!
It's so sad to look at.
Barteljaap all alone.
No, no, no!
Cancel 'Barteljaap all alone'!
Cancel! Cancel!
If you won't tell anyone...
then I won't either.
Door open!
Sad Barteljaap, all alone.