SOBBING
The Lord was my shepherd.
And now the Lord is dead, the poor beast.
And normally I would be very happy for the Lord...
because he would have gone to a better place.
But apparently everything has changed.
I no longer know what to believe in.
The Lord is with the Lord.
And the Lord will accept the Lord and in turn...
the Lord will accept the Lord as the Lord.
What do you mean by that?
Well, just.
Your dog is with God.
Oh, don't talk such rubbish, man.
That is what I mean, Mr. Hulst.
Normally when I hear "talk" and "rubbish," I'm already on my knees. And now?
Now nothing.
Well, not nothing. You're still a woman, you do get wet.
But... DEEP SIGH
Something has changed. Certainly. I can't teach anymore.
I no longer want to dance to the pipes... Pipes. Still nothing.
Yes, a little bit wet.
From those so-called scientists who claim
that a monkey did it with an ape...
and that we are descended from that.
You can reason that everything descends from an amoeba.
TALKING OVER EACH OTHER
Ans, Beertje, Mr. uhm... I also feel that something is changing. Look at me.
Sure, you see my swag. Of course.
But it is not the same dirty, indifferent swag as before.
Anyway, I know what it is about.
That which we held to be impossible has happened.
Tim and Erik are having an argument.
This is the work of Satan! Oh, dryness.
In the exceptionally sensitive ecosystem that I have created at this school...
everything is interconnected.
The suicide rate among first-year students has never been this high.
Everyone is so sad, no one can perform anymore.
Today are the final exams.
And if Tim and Erik are not brought together before the final English exam...
then all students will fail.
And then we can close the school!
Bring Tim and Erik together.
That is our mission!
Understood. BEEPING SOUND
I thank you for the trust.
I will not let you down.
The windows are shining like a mirror again.
Just as Tim and Erik's friendship will shine again.
OMINOUS TONES
Tim.
Pffff.
COUGHING Silence please in the library.
Got it.
Got that too.
Yeah, I roughly have that too. Marietje, this is not normal.
Even without those cheat sheets I did very well.
I am going to pass Dutch too. I only have ONE exam left, English.
If I get a 4 for that now...
I am still going to graduate.
Ow, my pussy. Aw.
Uh... Oh, that is incredibly good, Tim.
I'm proud of you.
Yes, Erik thought he could screw me over by leaving me behind alone...
but this boy is just going to graduate.
I am going to win you back with my intelligence.
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Ssssh.
Maria? Maria? I find books scary.
I have a work of art and also a question for you.
What is he looking at?
Pfff, that you even dated him. I was sad, Tim.
And Armani made me feel that I was special.
That when we were together there was nothing else besides him and me.
Huh?
But quite quickly I found out that it would not be forever.
Oh, so that tattoo is fake? No, that was just stupid.
But why did you spell it wrong? This is how you write Armani.
You should know how they write champagne.
You have given me black magic thing. I am going to you...
Hoooee. Aaah!
Hi.
Silence in the library!
As much as I like talking to you, Marietje...
I have a mission. For three weeks I've been speaking English nearly all day.
Three hours left before the final exam. I'm going to work.
EXCITING TONE
Hello. FART SOUND Oh, sorry.
We have to help Erik.
No, thank you. I want nothing more to do with Erik.
But he is your best friend. Yes, and I miss him.
But he has become an unreliable, humorless traitor.
It's not his fault. It's his mustache.
What? I read a book in the library...
stating that a mustache at a young age...
Wait a minute, you read a book?
You can't even read, can you?
No, but Onno can.
But he can't talk, can he?
No, but he can write.
But you can't read that, can you?
No, but Onno can.
Yes...
But then why doesn't Erik take that mustache off himself?
Erik has been taken over by his mustache.
Help us Tim. Destroy the mustache, destroy the evil.
Yes, sorry. I am choosing my school career.
Oh Tim...
Choosing for your school career.
You make me wetter than Mrs. Spek at first-year camp.
Do you know your English?
Yes!
Oh yeah?
Are you ready for your exam?
I can give you an exam.
Multiple choice.
First you only had this choice.
Now you're about to graduate, you have multiple choices.
Follow me, bad boy.
I'm for, Onno is against.
What are you?
I am by definition not for or against anything...
I think it is certainly important in this time
to seek nuance in the public debate.
Furthermore, I need to know what the statement is...
before I decide to be for or against.
The statement is:
Disabled children of failed asylum seekers...
may use drones as euthanasia during gay marriages.
And that's how it went.
While Erik was thinking, I robbed him of his mustache.
Tim and Erik can become friends again...
and then everything will be as it was again.
That's great news, Eddie. Here.
It's 100 euros.
A 100-euro coin.
Can I see it?
Eh... No, the mustache.
Oh, sorry.
Wooo, uncanny.
I also shaved off his other mustache just to be safe.
What?
KNOCKING
I had to come for a moment?
Yes, thanks for coming.
And have a good journey back.
Childish.
Oh yes, Eddie...
I am for. Okay.
Erik is now on his way to the gym. The final exams are about to start.
I leaked to China that his mustache works as a potency enhancer.
They could invade at any moment.
I spread a rumor on the deep web
that Erik's mustache insulted the prophet.
The entire universe could implode, Eddie.
THUNDERCLAP
Stop! I have a brilliant idea.
My cousin, Punny Willem, is in town.
Punny Willem? Doesn't he live with Tom?
They've broken up. Ah...
One night Tom was sitting on his swivel chair in front of the television.
And Punny Willem didn't want that.
So he turned Tom around.
And if you turn Tom around, you get "mot." (Dutch for conflict/clash)
BADA-BUM-TISH.
He is the only one who can save us. This will be funny, pun-ny.
Who was that friendly young man?
MUSIC
CHURCH BELLS TOLL
Erik, you have to fail this exam... Where is your mustache?
Punny Willem just took it.
Punny Willem? Yes, Punny Willem.
He taped my mustache onto his bike so he can go faster.
MUMBLING: "Snorfiets." (Dutch for moped/mustache-bike)
I found that quite funny just now, but actually I hate puns.
Yeah, okay. But you have to fail this exam.
Why? Tim is absolutely not going to make it.
He looks pretty self-assured otherwise.
Yes, fantastic man. She drags me into that toilet, third stall.
I pull those dungarees up, big underpants down.
I push her forward...
Believe me. Otherwise he'll be sitting here alone next year.
Why is he going to fail then?
I just had sex with Tim for the first time. Nice.
And I was dirty talking very nicely in English...
and at a certain point I shout five times:
Wrong hole, wrong hole.
But he doesn't understand any of it.
And at a certain point she is so horny...
she starts shouting incomprehensible things:
Rhaharhaharhaha!
Brilliant.
Pfff, tight though man. Ay-ay-ay.
SNIFFLING
Anyway, I've been deflowered.
Anyway, I'm still a virgin.
But I mean it, you can't leave him in the lurch.
But what if he does pass and I'm sitting here on my own.
Erik, he... Marietje, we're going to start. Would you please sit down?
Can I stand too?
Nice.
MUSIC
MUSIC: I DO IT FOR YOU BRYAN ADAMS
Ow!
WHIP SOUND
Ha ha ha!
Haaaa!
DEEP SIGH AND SOUND OF WATER
MUSIC: I DO IT FOR YOU BRYAN ADAMS
I don't understand it at all.
He had drawn some kind of weird thing, with an incomprehensible little text.
And now I've studied like crazy and I'm going to pass brilliantly...
and Erik will be staying back on his own. Why did he do that?
Because I asked him to. Huh?
Because I felt that he couldn't
leave you to stay back all by yourself.
But I'm not staying back at all! You ruined everything.
Erik is my absolute best friend ever and it's not going to be okay anymore.
Thanks to you. Well done, Marietje!
I did brilliantly on the exams. English went best of all.
I probably have a 10!
Yes...
That's a 10. Right?
No, that's a 10.4.
All added together. Oh.
Forget that 0.4 you got for English.
Oh yes! That is still higher than a 10.
Ah well, I'll have a new chance next year.
And I have you.
Tim, I'm sorry.
I always had the dream that I would marry you...
my childhood sweetheart.
and that we would then grow old together...
and that one day we would
move to Morocco with a whole bunch of Dutch people...
to ruin that country.
But as much as I find you sweet, and cute...
and funny.
You're just too stupid for me.
No. Marietje, I am very smart.
Yes. Look, these grades reflect... Hey!
They don't reflect how intelligent I actually am.
I am so smart.
Really, Tim?
Yeah, who am I kidding, I have no idea what you just said.
Wow, Tim.
You just completely ruined all your exams.
Yes. Sorry, man!
Whoa, that's...
What?! Did you get a 0.4 for English?
I had a 1.2, but I had drawn a cunt!
TO HIMSELF: Oh, a cunt.
Then what did you do?
Yeah... also made a very mean drawing.
Anyway, we're staying back.
Staying back! Staying back! GORILLA NOISES
Things were actually going very badly for me for a bit.
I went to a place I'd rather not have gone because of that mustache...
Hey guys! Do you have a pun?
Because I want one.
Get it? I. Willem.
Yeah, but what I was saying.
Hey guys!
Worst cheese scenario.
Get it?
Worst. Cheese. Scenario.
Try pronouncing it in English.
WITH ENGLISH ACCENT: Worst case scenario.
That doesn't mean anything, Willem!