PROM TONIGHT,
I NEED YOU. KISSES.
Barteljaap, are you ready
for tonight? Proms!
Listen, make sure at half past 10 exact...
you are at the stage, because then we...
- No, don't say.
But it's so cool!
- I know!
Just a little teaser.
- Alright then.
I won't say anything, but we'll
perform the coolest act. EVER.
I'm excited, guys.
I'm a little anxious, because...
this is my very first party ever.
Bartoujaabe.
- Bartoujaabe.
Bartoujaabe, don't
worry. You're the boss.
You'll be the king of the dancefloor.
You could get any woman.
Literally nothing could go wrong for you.
Listen Barteljaap, the
women here are just eager.
They're nothing but whores.
And they want you.
Barteljaap.
You're so handsome.
You know that, right?
You're a prince.
Before the party's starting, we'll
have a pre-drink at Tim's house.
Pre-drink!
Yo, yo, yo! This is DJ Video!
I wanna see you party!
Three, two...
Three, two, one, let's go!
Show your school ID.
I left it at home.
But, you know me.
I'm in your class.
- Beat it!
Show your school ID.
But Mr. Platje...
It's about to rain and I left it at
home, which is an hour long flight!
You're going, or tomorrow
your face in mesh!
We're the best guards.
We're letting no one in.
Muggles.
Barteljaap.
Are you sitting comfortably?
Tonight, we're going to kiss.
We?
No, silly, of course not.
Although, if you want to...
Of course. My boyfriend wouldn't mind.
Germans like wieners too, you know.
Of course.
But I meant at the prom, of course.
At a prom like this,
you of course have to...
kiss the whole night away.
I think I'm going home.
I think you have a crush on someone.
Don't you, Barteljaap?
Yes, but... It's not allowed.
I need to restrain myself.
When my father got hanged...
And my mom got shaven bald...
Little Heydrich got
taken to the Netherlands...
by two very sweet Chinese men.
Ka and Wing.
And the first night...
I slept with them in the basement...
they told me...
you're gay.
But I didn't really feel that at all, no.
I was so very in love with
all the girls, of course.
But they kept insisting that I was gay.
And I kept denying.
And every single day I got confronted
with all kinds of homophilic activities.
And I resisted, and I shivered,
and I didn't want to...
and I said: Nein, nicht
wieder in meine popo.
Everything's filled up already.
But those lovely sweethearts kept on
believing in my hidden away homosexuality.
And then...
After five years,
I still remember.
It was the afternoon, second session...
And just before Wing sat on my face...
Ka said his daily mantra...
If you endure this every single day...
then you must be gay.
Then something snapped like
a thick green bean in my head.
I turned gay.
What's your point?
That you should never suppress
your true feelings, of course.
And that Asian people are
very sweet and trustworthy.
Here, have a drink.
Life's so short, Barteljaap.
Today might just be your last.
What's the worst that could happen?
Komm, fohrt machen.
Just a little drink.
But your mouth doesn't get a period.
Get lost.
Here. My ID.
Can I come in now?
- No.
Why not?
- You said we're muggles.
Aren't you?
All year he waits for a
letter from Hogwarts.
But letter doesn't come.
You know why?
Because we don't have permanent
place. We're off the grid.
I can even talk to animals.
They do everything I say.
Sorry.
Can I come in now, then?
- No.
You say to Dumbledore...
he accept Armani, Hufflepuff.
Then you can come in. Or get lost.
Dumbledore is dead.
Go away! Get lost! Now!
Hey, guys!
You were right. Tonight's my night.
10:30, your act, right?
I just had some alcohol,
I'll get some cola now.
Stagedive!
Such, such a shame.
I wonder what your parents
would say if I told them this.
Gosh, your 14, goddamnit.
Is the booze still too strong for you?
I just took a hit of a nice spliff, too.
You don't see me complaining. Come on.
Erik, piss off. This is the girls' toilet.
What the fuck?
Sorry, I'm just...
Oh, Brinte. Hi.
- Hey.
Are you alright?
- I'm doing great.
Especially now I can see you again.
- What'd you say?
When I got your note, I was
certain you love me too.
What? Note?
- So nobody asks me...
how I'm doing. I'm just a middleman.
Even my mom and dad only raised me...
because they wanted to be grandparents.
But well...
I'm gay.
And I really want to be gay with you.
What are you saying? You have
to speak up. I can't hear you.
You're the only person who's
actually shows interest in me.
Who looks me in the eyes.
I want to hold you.
I want to kiss you.
I love you, Barteljaap.
I love you too.
But we need to wait until you're 18.
Eighteen?
No. I mean...
Nevermind. I'll tell her myself.
Thanks for the message.
Yes, boys and girls...
Come stand at the stage.
Let's start kissing!
Play the music!
You're the boss, Barteljaap.
Tonight's your night.
Pedo.
Pedo. Pedo.
No. No, but we love each other!
Police! Move!
You don't touch kids.
Stop him, mighty hare.
Go, Barteljaap. I'll hold them back.
Barteljaap killed Cookie!
I'm sorry, Brinte.
Murderer!
- Murderer!
No.
- Move!
Mr. Heydrich.
What happened?
Well, what has happened, Barteljaap?
You and your schmutzig-y hands...
touched an 11-year-old girl.
But we didn't kiss.
No, but you wanted to.
And that might be even worse.
But she wanted too.
Comfort and I...
love each other.
When she's 18, we'll marry.
So this might be a funny thing to hear...
Comfort has been hired by me.
What?
Sorry I get so excited about this
while you're startled, Barteljaap.
Startle-jaap.
But I worked on this
plan for three months.
And it was succesful.
Plan?
Yes.
It all started with that note
you got, written by me.
Getting to the teachers' lounge
was of vital importance to you.
But I didn't let you in.
You see, it's just a very simple technique
to make someone feel like an outsider.
And that's how you met Comfort.
Also lonely and innocent.
And I knew you would care
for her like a mother duck.
You finally weren't alone anymore.
But how could I tighten that connection?
More intensive.
Tears, Barteljaap.
It's very simple, really.
Tears.
You cared for her...
and when someone at
school would hurt you...
Who was always there for you?
Mr. Heydrich's personal helping hand...
Comfort.
But you didn't really let her into
that special place in your heart.
Your old identity and its associated
norms and values had to be demolished.
And that's why I had your sister killed/
Cupboard open.
Batskelien!
No!
You were at rock bottom.
And from there, I could
build you up again.
And when I started touching
that sweet, dear Comfort...
you revealed your true
feelings of her to me.
You punched me down.
You were the school's hero...
and I was that poor...
poor, poor Mr. Heydrich.
But that poor Mr. Heydrich knew
that you were listening at the wall.
After that it was very simple.
Act sad, some tears,
politely listening to you...
I had won over your trust.
I also found a translator online, and
started paying Comfort even more...
to say some really dirty things.
She's a nasty girl.
Very nasty.
She'll do anything for money.
And with a simple trick, I made
little Remi point in her direction.
And yes, that's it.
Pedo.
I'm not a pedo.
But I made you believe it, right?
And did you notice how the word
"pedo" silently nested itself...
into your subconcious?
Then, tonight came.
I just had to invite that translator
to push you into the right direction.
I sneakily said "Comfort" a few times.
Are you comfortable?
Komm, fohrt machen.
I made everyone head to the dancefloor...
I called the police beforehand...
Meanwhile I also planted the word
"pedo" in your head. Do you remember?
Come stand at the stage.
Let's start kissing!
Pedo music!
And of course I played a song
that you're very familiar with.
By the way, did you notice that
with all positive experiences...
always the color...
babyblue appeared?
That babyblue space, created
by Mr. Heydrich himself.
That's where Barteljaap
felt safe and strong.
And that's where all implanted
pedofeelings came together in a...
very painful and illegal climax.
Well, and now we're here.
Yeah.
Operation...
Break Barteljaap...
ist abgeschlossen.
And by the way, that story
of the two Chinese men...
who would've turned me gay...
that's not true.
Or maybe it is?
Why?
- Why?
That's a great question. I just
like doing these kinds of things.
What are you?
I am a spider.
Welcome...
to my web.
I'll get you to a hospital.
You will make it. Believe me.
I don't know what to believe.
I don't know what's real anymore.
This is real. My love
for you. That's real.
You might be... the only one...
who truly loves me.
Be glad that someone
loves you, Barteljaap.
Brinte...
I love...
No.
Are you the translator?
Could you tell me what you saw?
I invoke my G-code.
I don't talk to pigs.
I'm no snitch, nigga.
Done.