One, two. One, two. Mic test.
Wow, yo! What up? What up?
Pra pra pra in the building. Yo!
FOR AFRICA
Alright school, listen up.
As a result of the events
surrounding Lars, over here...
Viktor and I have
something to say.
We want...
Mazoezi Mwalimu and I
have something to say.
Well, all the best.
Hey, Erik. How...
With wearing the stupidest outfit ever.
We're not going to sleep yet.
Rather pyjamas than a
weird crop top.
My mom used the
wrong washing program.
Lars is a regular, ordinary student.
Just like everybody else.
Lars would like to be treated that way.
And we would like that  too.
He is not an exception.
And that's why we want to do
something special, just for Lars.
I'm passing the mic to Mazoezi.
Yo! Hulst out.
Shame.
Disgust.
Disappointment.
Lars was called a monkey.
And you all said nothing.
Someone said that Lars came
from the anus of a gay man.
And you all did nothing.
Evil doesn't prosper through
the doings of one bad  person.
But through the silence of
100 good people.
No talking is talking too.
Doing nothing is something too.
And that's why you will refrain
from eating for 24 hours.
You will show solidarity to Lars,
to me, and everyone from our country.
Right, Lars?
I've arranged sponsors.
All the money raised will
go towards charity.
Ask your questions to
the people in charge.
Stand up.
Two fists in the air for Africa!
This is amazing. Now I can find
out whether the legend is true.
Which of the hundred?
- That at this school, after midnight...
Peter Jan Rens is performing
without an audience.
No, not that one. That after midnight...
Young thugs get together to
talk about their feelings.
Nope. That after midnight,
at a secret location...
a fashion heaven opens.
For anyone who's short on clothes.
- At ridiculously low prices.
I've been searching for years.
I'll get something new for us both,
since this is one sorry look.
Mary, what's the matter?
Are you ignoring me?
I dislocated my shoulders.
What the fuck?
What a whore.
She jerked someone off, for sure.
We will now have ten minutes of silence.
For my country, Africa.
Africa isn't even a country.
Alright, that's racist.
You get detention.
I'm not even in your class.
- Double detention.
Then what's my name?
Hu...frens...
Kin..derindrinderik.
Shit! How did he know?
Suck it,
Hufrenskinderindrinderik!
For having the worst name ever!
- Shut up!
Harakiri has the worst name ever.
Then, you have to divide the circle's
circumference by its diameter.
You can measure the diameter
with your ruler.
So that would be the diameter-meter.
90 seconds left!
Hey, Mary.
You jerked off someone else,
didn't you? Who is it?
What's his name? Why?
What's wrong with me? Is he strong?
Not that I'm jealous.
I bet he's a loser. I'm long over you.
Mary, Mary...
Do you want to date?
I'm so glad that I don't have to listen
to this childish whining anymore.
And I now have a relationship
with a mature adult.
Is it an adult? Is it a teacher?
Mary. Mary.
Since you're all so
busy eating...
I'll enjoy it myself too.
Happy birthday, Barteljaap.
You're a sweetheart.
You can make a wish.
I wish that everyone...
would be nice to each other.
And that my diabetes would
be cured, of course.
Hakuna matata, school!
The hunger strike starts now.
Starting now, there will be
no more drinking and eating.
No, Barteljaap! No!
I'll never eat again.
Oh, I'm so hungry.
I'm so done.
I need to save my energy to
kill Mary's new boyfriend.
You don't even know who it is.
- I do, it's an adult.
There are so many of them.
Look, Erik. I know her technique.
Look for someone
with a weird walk.
Why is your dick in a cast?
A cast? This is my penis-socket.
Then what's that walk for?
That's a white person's remark.
Try putting your dick in
an electrical socket.
Barteljaap!
I've always been nice to you.
That's all over now.
If you let Mary touch you
for even one more time...
or if you touch her with
your dirty fingers, then...
That never happened.
- Keep calm. Restrain yourself.
No way.
I didn't even touch you.
Are you seriously flopping?
- Sugar.
Sugar? No, you can't have that.
- Sugar is food too. It's prohibited.
Yes. Food.
Diabetes.
Diameters?
- Stop it with the maths. School's out.
Could you not touch me? Who knows
what else your dirty hands touched.
Insulin.
- In Celine?
That's disgusting,
Barteljaap!
Celine is only twelve and she
is having a hard time at home.
Mary, Celine. Don't you have any dignity?
You're sick. That's what you are.
That's what I'm trying to say.
- Leave him be.
You're a sexual predator!
No...
I've never been touched
by a woman.
Hungry!
You don't know hunger.
To you, hunger is just a word.
The African language has
28 words for hunger.
Alright?
Thank you.
Pizza, pasta, pancakes, pie.
Anything starting with a P.
Fashion heaven isn't under the
soccer field or the maths classroom.
The gym hall would stand out too much.
Oh my god, Erik.
Sportlehrer!
Where are the bandages?
I have some schwanzschmertz.
It's in the gym hall.
- Dirty piece of...
Then I'm off to the gym hall, ja?
I will destroy his office.
- Calm down.
Let's get the facts straight.
Then we get a new sweater.
He said he's in the gym hall.
Let's destroy his office now.
We'll get that sweater later.
- It is Heydrich talking.
He just says he's in the gym hall,
for us to go to his office.
That way he'll punish us.
But I know that he knows that you
would say that, so he's in the gym hall.
But he knows that you would say that,
so he's definitely in his office.
But he knows that you'd say that,
so he is in the gym hall.
Yeah, that's true.
Welcome, guys.
Come, take a seat.
Weren't you in the gym hall?
But I already knew that you'd
think that I'd think...
that you'd think, anyhow...
It's just us three now.
There's nothing in it.
No way. We're not doing this.
Because we're Africans today.
Oh, really?
How happy they must be
with that. More Africans.
Then take the envelope next
to you and mail it to Africa.
Bone dry strasse,
house number eins, Africa.
ZIP code: Eins, zwei,
drei, vier, funf...
HUNGER.
And keep waving those hands to avoid
the malaria mosquitoes, Africans.
You're supposed to be in the gym
hall for African board games.
Yeah, you're overseeing No Moneyopoly
and The Game of Strife.
You can't read, because you're
Africans. Keep going. Got it?
Don't lick your fingers.
Wipe it in the envelope.
Ja?
And what if I do eat it?
Oh, then I will snitch
you out of course.
Oh, because then I'm telling everyone
that you touch little girls.
I really hoped that you would say that.
I really did. Because I
have a surprise for you.
I'll be going away.
I can't handle the
pain that will ensue.
Oh, one more thing...
Das Essen ist poisoned, naturlich.
Did you hear? Mary had
to go home. She ate.
She ate a banana.
She sucked a bit on the lollipop.
She had a little cream.
She ate a few seeds.
She had a bit of the
protein shake.
I'm tired.
I'll go sleep in the gym hall.
Fucking hell. How many bad innuendos
for a blowjob even are there?
What?
Oh, dear Comfort.
You saved my life.
Eating through a tube is cheating!
Damnit!
Mazoezi, stop it!
Was that an order? Master.
It was. Now, get lost!
Are you seeing this? The oppression?
Overthrow the white regime!
Stay there, white man.
Kill the whites!
Stop this act, Mazoezi.
Put that spear away.
Power to the people!
- Put that spear away.
No, no. Don't do that.
That's my spear.
Viktor, I'm sending you on
paid leave for a while.
I think that's best for now.
You can't do that to me, please. You
can't take the school away from me.
I'm just joking. I don't know what
I'm saying. Look at what I'm wearing.
Viktor.
- No, please. No.
Just tell me what
you want. I'd do anything.
I'm just a dumb African.
I'm very obedient.
Viktor, it's over. Forget what I said.
I'm not sending you on paid leave.
I'm firing you.
No, no, please. You can't do
that to me. I beg of you.
Guys! I love all kids.
Lars! Please.
Say... Lars...
Do I really need to go, Lars?
Viktor, it's over. Get lost. I don't
want to see you ever again.
Except for the soccer tournament.
As left back.
Then who's midfield?
Papa. Now fuck off!
Guys, school is almost starting.
Lars.
You can't punch
Armani in his face.
Come, let's get a new sweater...
- No, stop it!
There is no fashion heaven.
I don't need new clothes.
But you promised...
- Fuck off, Erik!
Sorry, I'm just so hungry.
- That's okay. I'm hungry too.
I'm going shopping.
I'll be back in a jiffy.
Take care.
Thank you.
It made me sad that you didn't
show up for my birthday, Bilal.
I drew the invitations myself.
I bought a nice cake, too.
Hungry.
Where is the fashion heaven?
Ask your questions to
the people in charge.
Questions? So many questions.
Pizza, pasta, pancakes, pie.
Anything starting with a P.
P? Peeing, pooping.
I'm Barteljaap. I'm gay.
I'm a twinkie.
PETER JAN RENS:
♪ Show your hands
Show your teeth
♪ Did you clean them well?
Did you clean them well?
♪ Show your brains
And show your feet
♪ Are they fresh and neat?
♪ Show your behind
And show your shoes
I'm going to the toilet. I'll be telling
Tim. But you don't know that yet.
Toilet. Peeing. Pooping.
The toilet. The toilet!
Tim?
Help. I was searching for fashion heaven.
I need to go to the toilet.
Small stinky or big stinky?
Very big stinky.
I'm tired. I'll go sleep in the gym hall.
TOILETS | GYM HALL
So...
Will you help me?
Come with me.
Hello?
Hey!
Mr Hulst?
What are those clothes?
Isn't it beautiful?
I found it in fashion heaven.
So it does exist?
Yeah.
But where is it?
No other student has ever been
close to it as often as you.
Come on, Eric. Keep your head up.
Hallelujah!
I'm sorry, Armani. I need to
send you away. You ate something.
What I don't get, though...
I get that you're hungry.
You just want to eat something.
But why eat shit?
You see...
It was Eddy...
- I don't want to hear it.
So you didn't blow him?
No.
Armani talks shit.
But you two are... dating?
Yeah.
Life goes on, Tim.
And I love you too. So very much.
No. I meant that you need to move on.
I'm sorry.
Mary. Please.
Tim! Tim!
I found it.
Fashion heaven is real.
I got something for you, too.
Oh, nice!
It's so beautiful. It's... magical.
Fashion heaven.
Can I get out now?
Guys, the hunger strike is over.
Well done.
Could you imagine....
those poor, poor Africans.