Someone puked in the hallway.
You surely know why I
have called you here.
I believe this to be
a very ordinary school.
And it's customary to
keep yourself to the rules.
But what isn't customary,
is the use of violence.
Joppe Poederbach.
Of course, you can have a discussion.
Sometimes you hate someone.
But what you did...
is something I've never seen before
during my years as vice principal.
Strolling into the bushes
to find a nice oak stick...
walk up to your ex and wave
that stick in front of her face...
and without any emotion at all...
I can't bear myself to say it.
yell Avada Kedavra!
One of the three
unforgivable curses.
I've alerted the Ministry.
You'll be banished to Azkaban today.
Anthony!
[mumbling]
The Dark Lord shall return.
Anthony.
Anthony, get him out of here.
I'm afraid I won't let that happen.
A euro!
Joppe Poederbach!
They put the dot
between their eyebrows...
because it symoblizes the third eye.
I'm sorry.
I just thought that we
only have two eyes.
Anyways, continue.
The dot is called a bindi.
Forget about Mary, Tim.
You can get any girl you want.
You're the jackpot.
The jackpot of the local bingo, maybe.
- Dude.
You're tall. You have blue eyes.
You've got nice, thick hair.
When you laugh, there's a
super cute gap in your front teeth.
Look, there it is.
So that's why they believe that the
dot protects them and their partners.
So.
I think the beauty of Hinduism is that...
everything that lives,
gets a lot of respect.
Many Hindus are vegeterian,
and some animals...
have a special position
in their religion, like the cow...
which are holy.
Such nonsense!
A holy cow.
Hindus believe that humans would've
never existed without the cow.
Hey, Mary. Did you know that
those crazy Hindus believe...
that the cow, just because it's
"holy", can predict the future?
Oh, well, Ms. Cow, can you tell
me if I'll live a happy life?
And then the cow will say:
maybe if you started...
searching for a job, instead
of talking to a cow.
Humans would've never
existed without the cow...
because the cow provides milk.
- And do you know how they thank the cow?
By sticking a bouquet of
flowers up its ass!
Because the cow provides
milk, and also manure.
And do you know what
they also do to those cows?
Jesus Christ.
Could she please finish her sentence?
- Blasphemy, Tim!
I'm very disappointed. Twenty!
Twenty? Goddamnit.
Silence!
That's cursing! Make it double.
Thirty? Jesus.
Make it fifty!
Fifty? Come on...
That's it! Homophilia!
Fifty for the both of you.
That was wonderful.
Amazing stand-up. You're funny.
Let's continue our class.
Jehovas.
I could go on.
Nine, ten.
You also have a really nice ass.
- Thank you.
Hey guys. I apparated
here real quick.
You as my student-mentors need to help me.
Hulst wants to send me to Azkaban.
Calm down, Joppe Poederbach.
We'll go talk to Hulst.
Really?
Would you do that for me?
Of course, Joppe Poederbach.
That's what we're here for. Right, Tim?
Fifty.
We realize that you
were just playing along...
but we're concerned about the decisions
you made regarding Joppe Poederbach.
You see...
Joppe Poederbach takes those
books a little too seriously.
He's just a weird first-year.
He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named
was just a weird first-year, too.
And look at how he ended up.
All those casualties, and for what?
Anyhow, Joppe Poederbach
is devastated now.
Joppe Poederbach is a killer.
That girl is still alive,
everything's fine.
That's impossible.
There is only one person who has
ever survived the curse of death, and...
Mr Hulst, that's all made up.
Muggle talk.
I've never had to use this bad boy,
so don't make me do it, young man.
It's just a book.
It's not real, it's just been
written down by someone.
It's made up, Mr Hulst.
You can't talk with the painting
of the previous principal.
No.
And it's not like when
you kiss a frog...
Don't you have class?
- No, we have a free period.
You should be at
Ms. Glee's history class.
That's not true, we made
her incredibly depressed.
She's been gone for half a year.
She's been back for two months
already. Just look at the schedule.
Holy shit. Is Ms. Glee back?
We didn't even have time to put pubes
in her teabag. There's no time left.
Then I better get going too.
Were did you come from?
That's now relevant right now. She, er...
apparated.
Well, guys, go to class. Come on.
And no goofing around, please.
Be nice to Ms. Glee. She isn't
as depressed as before, but...
she feels a little down.
Hello class.
How fun! Paper balls!
You are sweet,
you all get an A.
An A? But why?
Why isn't she crying?
This is ridiculous.
- Why is she so happy?
We had just gotten her overworked.
Hey Mary.
Who is this?
Depression is a silent killer, guys.
You should've seen her at her worst.
Who wants to hug me?
It's horrible.
We need to get her normal self back,
because class is no fun like this.
Hey boy, did you lose something?
Tony said that I had spilled
something. So I need to clean it.
Oh, but I don't think
that this is yours.
I see darkness, Barteljaap.
It's coming for you.
I see tears, Barteljaap.
Ah, me too. I'm just going...
- Your tears.
Tears at a party.
Hey, Comfort. Are you sad?
Look at this.
Hey, what's that?
Yeah.
Barteljaap!
Witch!
Ringedingeding!
Armani, what is it?
This is the first time I
actually got everything.
Like you were talking a
different language before this.
Thank you, Miss.
We've come to apologize.
About everything.
We just want to see you
back to normal again.
All those stupid jokes
that made you so sad...
were ours.
Sorry we signed you
up for a datingsite...
with men wanting a
threesome with a pet.
Sorry we turned around
the door every class.
Sorry we taught your dog to shit
everytime his name is called.
Sorry we replaced your DVDs with
a movie of a man pinching his nipples...
whilst an organ is playing.
It was just wrong.
We regret that our actions
caused so much sadness.
I'm actually very happy.
We hear how heartbroken you are.
A thousand times sorry.
First I was sad, but I'm not anymore.
This isn't working. Let's
try something else.
What is it? It was worth a try.
It works in fairytales.
Let's go.
Viktor, what happened to you?
No, no. Viktor is no longer.
The name is Mazoezi Mwalimu.
Viktor means conqueror.
That reminds me of the oppresion.
Never again. The Viktorian era is over.
I'm a changed person.
- Viktor.
Quit it with this stupid stuff.
Let's go.
Hold on, wait.
A changed person, you say?
Of course. Everyone can change.
It's very simple.
Okay, how?
Only if you sing along to
the African anthem.
No.
- No?!
First you loot my country, and now
you can't even sing a song?
♪ It's gonna take a lot
to drag me away from you ♪
♪ There's nothing that a hundred men
or more could ever do ♪
You speak African?
- That was amazing.
Incredible. Thank you for that.
Listen up.
This is how the medicine man
in my village does it.
You put two tablespoons of flour
in a regular, ordinary bowl.
Some salt water, half
a liter of goat milk.
A handful of rice, just regular rice.
Two teaspoons of honey.
And the crushed bones of
a full-grown albino.
Got it?
Alright.
Barteljaap Gustaaf Balneger.
You stand trial here today...
in the precence of God...
for sorcery...
witchcraft...
seducing an underage girl...
to commit adultery.
Mr. Heydrich, don't you
know I'm not a witch?
Heydrich? I don't know
a Mr. Heydrich.
I'm the executioner.
- Come on, I can see it's you!
Ja, maybe in your little crystal ball.
I saw, ladies and gentlemen...
as God is my witness...
how this witch...
whilst possessed by the devil...
took on two completely
different faces!
How his fingers...
moved from one hand,
to the other hand.
How he made the filthy,
red balls of Satan...
conjure out of the body of that girl.
That's just a disappearing act.
I can also make things disappear.
Who's that?
That's Red Ronnie.
Whatever you give him...
- He puts up his ass.
Disgusting.
But you're a witch!
Witch, witch, witch!
In the name of God...
I convict you to burn
three times at the stake!
What is your answer to that?
No, no! I don't want that!
Help, help!
Satan can't hear you now,
Barteljaap.
Set fire to it.
- Jawohl!
Stop, stop! Don't do it.
Don't set fire to Barteljaap.
We need him.
Huh?
I'm not an albino at all!
Oh.
Eh...
Well, never mind.
Continue with what you were doing.
Nothing to worry about.
Stop, guys, stop!
You can't do this!
This is rediculous.
You can't suddenly say that
Barteljaap is a witch...
and burn him like that?
That's absurd!
Has history taught us nothing?
You should toss him into a lake
strapped to a boulder.
And if he floats to the surface,
he's actually a witch...
and you can burn him.
And what if he stays under the water?
Well, then, er...
Then he wasn't a witch.
But at least we know then.
How are you so sure about that?
I learned that today...
in history class.
What are you doing?
Just look at how proud Ms. Glee is.
Shame. I was looking
forward to the fireworks.
Drown him, drown him, drown him!
Drown him, drown him!
Drown him!
To the fireplace in
the teachers' lounge.
Witch, witch, witch!
Guys, guys. Listen to me for a second.
Guys, please listen to me for a bit.
Take Barteljaap out of
the water immediately.
Oh, wait a second. I just
want to explain why.
I just have to catch my breath.
What was it I wanted to say again?
Oh, right.
Speaking as vice-principal
of this school...
and also as a human,
too, actually, somewhat...
I just wanted to say... You in
the water, can you quiet down?
Can you please be quiet?
I'm trying to hold a speech.
Just a few words.
Guys, I learned something today.
I learned that things in a book...
aren't always true.
And that you shouldn't believe...
the things that a stranger
writes down in a book.
And also that the toilet should
really only be used for dumps.
Oh, and one more important thing.
Can I interest someone to
adopt my owl? It's a white owl.
50 euros. Hardly used. Nobody?
No one at all? Oh, well.
Alright then.
- Help, help!
What are you waiting for? Get
that man out of the water!
So, boys and girls. What
Mr. Hulst is trying to say is...
that this is crearly nonesense.
Sometimes things seem
to be supernatural...
but there is always a
logical explanation for it.
Witchcraft, sorcery:
it doesn't exist.
Just like how gnomes don't exist, and...
sorry to break it to you,
sister Innocentia,
God doesn't exist either.
Hey, ouch! Goddamnit!
Blasphemer! Heretic!
This is your punishment!
Don't you see that He is truly
everywhere, everytime?
And I'm talking about God!
God, the one and only!
And not about that mad Hindu!
Not that fatty of a Buddha!
Not Krishna, not Jahweh...
not Thor and definitely not about...
God, get me! Please, take me!
Look at that. Ms. Glee is back.
She's all back to normal.
Please, get me too!
Please!
I hate you all!
She's back to normal.
Release me!
All because of my kiss,
after all. I knew it.
No way.
She has been so touched because
she taught me something...
That she doesn't feel down anymore.
I'm such a special boy.