Look, it's all about one
thing: penetration.
Pinch the wingers,
tip over the backs...
and they'll be offside
before they know it.
Then all we have to do is
touch it, temporize it...
and ensure you can get three points.
I've waited my whole life for this.
You only get this chance
once every seven blue moons.
Do the necktie!
Sorry!
Hun, I hope your shot today
will be cut from a better tree.
Hey, Mary.
Will you be cheering for us?
That depends on whether
if my man is competing.
Can you stop this nonsense?
Don't tell me you
actually love him.
This says for itself.
That surely says for itself.
What about us?
Did you forget it all?
How we snatched cotton candy
from little Moroccans at the fair?
All those times that we nicked dates
and olives from the Moroccan store?
How we made clicking sounds to the
Moroccan girls at the swimming pool?
All those times you...
Don't stir up old wounds, Tim.
Stop it.
You forgot.
Walk.
Hey, let her go, Tim.
We need to get in the zone.
I'll get the ball.
It smells like poo.
Yo, Tim! Catch!
I'd rather not talk with the
opposing captains.
Especially on matchday.
But we need to take care
of some formalities.
At 1400, match.
Six against six. For 14 minutes..
For those 14 minutes,
I don't know you.
What happens on the field, stays on the
field. Even if I kick your kneecaps off.
After the match, we give
a modest handshake.
The winner receives, apart from
a night with Ms. Pepper...
and the 100 thousand euros
left over from the hunger strike...
a big ass cup.
Got it?
And the losers?
The losers?
They'll be unsexed.
Of course. Every sexual experience...
will be gone.
What's the threshold?
If you pissed over your friends
once in the locker room...
That's fine. Just a bit of laughs.
But did you do it to a girl?
That'll be gone.
Just everything you've got
written down in your book.
Gagging, gaping, gushing, gobbling...
scatting, squirting, choking, sniffing...
will all be gone.
So, err...
Getting jerked off?
- Gone.
Seeing Tessa's tits in sixth grade?
Oh really? Gone.
Fall down on the beach and cry to
be picked up by a topless woman?
Ah, fist bump.
Gone.
I once fingered a cat.
Gone, I think.
A text from your mom.
Dear class.
As you may already know...
I had to cremate my sister
Batskelien this weekend.
It's a pity that none of
you were able to come.
But I get it.
It was such a bad hailstorm, that
even the undertaker stayed home.
I did manage to carry
the coffin all by myself.
I am the last surviving Balneger,
and that name will die with me...
because I can't get kids.
But, dear class,
you are my children.
Through the knowledge
that I can give to you...
I will always live on through you.
That way, there will be a little bit
Balneger in every one of you.
I won't let you down.
Just today, the only thing
I'm asking of you is...
to let me finish speaking.
Just this once, guys.
It's time for the super fair draw
for the legendary soccer game...
that gets played once
every seven blue moons.
Mr. Hulst's Mannschaft constists of...
Just drawing a lot.
Armani.
Armani's father.
That's allowed, because he
teaches Latin as of right now.
Now pick two idiots,
otherwise it's suspicous.
And also Tony, Frederique and...
Just pick the fat one,
I'll make her goalie.
And Roslin.
And now Tim and Erik's team.
Lars.
Jet.
Eddy.
And Barteljaap.
And that was it.
We see each other at 2 o'clock!
Heil Hi-
We'll never win this.
- True.
We need a secret weapon.
You're not thinking of...
He is the best soccer player
that's ever been at this school.
But no one knows where...
Not even Hulst.
Otherwise he would've
drawn him in his team.
So if we can find him before Hulst does...
- Hi Viktor.
We're Tim and Erik.
I may be blind, but my other
senses are overdeveloped.
Unmistakenably.
Viktor.
Thank you, Eddy.
Huh? What?
Hello?
There's no one here. It's just...
Viktor...
it's us.
Hey. Tim en Erik.
What year is it?
2044.
But err... Viktor...
We need you.
The legendary 'once every seven
blue moons'-soccer game is today.
And we want you.
We would go on 'you', right?
- Yeah, sorry.
Without you, we're nothing.
There is a lot at stake.
No, I'm saving myself for Mr. Hulst!
I'm his left back!
Mr Hulst already has a left back, Armani.
That can't be.
Mr Hulst promised me I
could be his left back!
His team is complete.
He doesn't need you.
And we're here for you now, not Mr. Hulst.
And we, we want you.
You have no idea how
I survived all those years.
How many times I've begged for help.
- Just come with us, Viktor.
Just come here.
I hope you lose.
But I also hope the others lose.
Actually, I hope everyone loses.
Get AIDS.
What are you doing?
- We're playing a game.
Want to join?
- No.
I want to talk to you, Comfort.
I want to say goodbye.
I quit.
No more maths, no stupid soccer game.
I'm leaving, and I won't ever come back.
Of course. Pure favouritism.
Can we play again?
It's nearly my turn.
I tried everything,
but no one believes in me.
Goodbye.
I believe in you,
Barteljaap Balneger.
When I came here under
incredibly false pretenses...
lost both my kidneys in a bet and had
to work in the banana bar, did I give up?
No, Barteljaap. You know why?
Real strength comes from inside.
You need to fight, and take
matters into your own hands.
Then happiness will find you.
You're right, Comfort.
Taking matters into my own hands.
I had played soccer for 13 damn years.
I will show them the real Barteljaap.
I will score a goal, and
I'll dedicate it to you.
Alright, fine. Whatever.
Bye. Get on with it.
This round was invalid.
Have another go, Comfort.
Come on, guys!
Champagne. I'm Armani's
younger and older sister.
Hey, Armani's dad!
Say something in Latin!
Fuck, he really knows it.
Pregnant?
No shit.
How far along?
18 months.
It's twins.
And who's that?
That's Frederique.
- Correct, that's Frederique.
Listen, us three have to do the hard work.
We can give them a hard time, but...
my right ankle is weak...
and he has a bad hamstring.
Hey ref, they have a new player!
That's our substitute.
That's only allowed if someone's injured!
Do it.
Anything for the team.
I meant Jet.
Ref, we want Viktor in!
That's Viktor?
- Alright, guys.
Jeez, he looks different.
I won't let you down.
You took me from the darkness.
I will bring you to the light.
And Lars, I'm sorry about
everything that happened.
I said some things...
You said some things...
We were both wrong.
We can win this.
They have weaknesses too.
For example...
- Hey, Viktor!
You'll get your job back if
you keep a clean sheet.
No! Oh no, it's over.
We're never gonna win this.
- Tony!
A euro for a concussion!
Ref!
Injury. Substitution.
Alright, he can't run, and you
have to kick him on the ankle.
Boys.
Let me be goalie.
Get them, tiger!
Ref, time-out.
Alright boys, it's going great.
1 minute left and it's 0-0.
It's 17-0, Eddy.
Lars, Jet, Eddy, Barteljaap...
I know you've got nothing to lose.
Your books are empty.
But Erik and I...
We're big players.
This defeat doesn't only
mean losing a game...
This defeat means losing
stories and memories.
Memories which are important to us.
Which were taken away
due to Viktor's treason.
You heard what Hulst said.
Viktor gets his job back if
he keeps a clean sheet.
Let's not make that happen.
Let's spare no effort
to score just one point.
Let's leave the field as heroes.
And maybe, just maybe...
we all have something to write
down in our books tonight.
Alright? Come on!
BANNER
SOCCER
Kick! Kick!
- Kick it!
Kick it!
It's an open goal. Come on!
Here you go, Lars. You can have it.
You deserve it.
Damnit Viktor, you're
always making a mess.
Why are you like this?
Now beat it. Get off
the property. You're fired.
But... we kept a clean sheet, boss.
Get lost, move it!
They have seen me.
I have failed.
Test project QX143 is cancelled.
Project will return to home planet Era...
Third valley universe.
Of course.
So it was.
I was so confused.
He has white two dads,
but he's a different color.
That's not possible.
Mr. Hulst's team wins!
For me? No, really?
BIG ASS CUP
Don't you see? Everything I do fails.
Maybe it would be better if I...
If you what? Barteljaap?
If I were dead.
My name is Barteljaap...
I'm a sore loser and
that's why I want to die.
And what about this little fishcake?
- Don't touch her!
Are you going to abandon her?
Shall Herr Heydrich play
with her after school?
Don't touch her!
I could.
Then she'll finally get a real man.
Now it's over.
I'm not letting myself
get walked over! Darn it!
Sorry.
Barteljaap! Barteljaap! Barteljaap!