Autumn.
The air is pregnant with hormones.
By peeing on himself he
emphasizes his status and masculinity.
And throwing a lot of grass in the
air also makes a deep impression.
They look at each other.
Well, I told you so.
That is a lot more impressive
for them than for us.
Let's see what nature further
has in store for that kind of behavior.
He's looking around
with just one thought.
I would take Roslin at this point.
- Is it that bad?
It's off the charts. I'm always almost
there, but she teases me so much.
Just look at her.
Ohhh, look at that.
Yeah, dude. Hot.
Nature, boys and girls,
is just one big dating site.
You just have to clearly say
what you want. Just say:
I want to fuck.
Who wants to fuck me?
Please, someone.
Fuck me. Who? Who wants to fuck me?
If he asks one more time,
then I'll do it.
Fuck? Who?
And there is already one
coming. It's that easy.
Or is it that easy?
No, there we go.
Typical female behavior.
They leave. Don't want to, headache.
Hey, Mary. Now look at
this. Just be a good girlfriend.
Goddammit, Erik. I'm doing a performance.
That's a damn craft. Report
to vice-principal Hulst.
It's unbelievable, isn't it? In the
middle of a fucking bio-performance.
Tim, what are you doing?
We got kicked out, right?
- Just Erik, not you.
Ooo!
Now you too. Get out.
Breathe low.
Thank you.
Guys, this is the second time
today that you've been here.
Half past nine.
There is no point in sweeping
the schoolyard twice in one day.
There is something else you can do for me.
You've probably heard that I
reeled in Ms. Salt, right?
Yep, big time.
I gave something to her and
she gave me something too.
The fame and money of the vice-principal.
Those women think it's wonderful.
But now Ms. Salt started bitching
about getting into a relationship...
And I'm also dating my ex again.
And Frederique of course.
No, it's fine. I had it looked into
by my lawyer.
She had to re-do the year. It's all good.
But now Salty has to get dumped.
And you'll be the ones to do that.
Aren't you an adult?
- So what?
You can do that yourself, right?
I did that in first grade, breaking
up for someone else.
You've been sent out of class.
You're going to do it.
Not it.
Listen, Mr. Tree...
I appreciate that Mr. Hulst
arranged this tutoring.
But Lars won't be a problem.
He's such a very sweet animal.
That's exactly what I mean.
What is this?
A drawing.
Yes, of what?
Um... a man.
A man, but of what species?
Just uh...
a human.
- Very good, Viktor. Yes.
And what is this?
- A monkey.
Viktor, the drawing doesn't change.
- No.
Pay close attention to the figure.
- Yes.
What is this?
A human.
Yes, and take a good look, Viktor.
One, two.
A monkey.
So that's not quite right yet.
We'll do it again, alright?
A human.
A monkey. A human.
A monkey. A human. A monkey.
A human. A monkey.
Pong Feng.
Ahhh, wrong button.
I don't know eh...
Wait, wait.
The big guns.
Hello, Viktor.
Mr. Tree?
- Hello, Viktor.
So that's why Salt didn't want me.
She was occupied with Hulst.
But you heard him,
Salty has to get dumped.
No. Listen, Erik.
We can't hurt her. My only
passing grade is from Salt.
Please let's be very nice.
Alright, but I want to be there,
'cause I wanna see that bitch burn.
We have to handle this really
fucking sensitively.
Hulst, man.
Who knows everything
about being dumped?
Your mom.
- Yes, and...
Your stepmother.
Your father's secretary.
- As well. And?
Ahhh!
Hey, Barteljaap.
We just need your help.
O! Yes, of course.
About Chapter 11?
- No, it's more of a private problem.
O? And you want to talk with me...
Don't you want your mentor to...
- No, this is only possible with you.
Well, wow. I'm listening. Yes.
Look, you really are a nerd.
- Such a nerd. It's ridiculous.
We need to break up with a lady.
You have obviously been
dumped many times in your life.
What's the best way to get dumped?
Be short, be concise, be
honest, but not too honest.
Breaking up is painful enough in itself.
Kicking a dead horse is unnecessary.
Haha, Barteljaap. We had a bet
on who could get the biggest nerd.
Haha, Barteljaap. Your
parents paid me to be with you.
Haha, Barteljaap.
Now you've got AIDS too.
Barteljaap is such a poser.
- We're not going to do it like that.
We'll just dump that chick with a note,
against your wishes.
She deserves that.
- What?
You want to break up with me?
No, no.
- With a note?
Do I mean so little to you?
Fuck you!
Fuck you very much!
You suck!
- Mary, that wasn't about you at all.
It was about Ms. Salt.
What?
- I love you.
You're my little doe.
I want to throw grass for you...
and bash my head into
someone else's head.
And I want to run after
you screaming all day long.
And I want to piss all over
myself and if that's not enough...
then I want to piss all over you too.
Really?
- Yes.
You're coming with me.
We have to be with Salt in one minute.
- I'll make that easily.
When Jonah was sat in the whale
One...
two...
three.
Oh, you're there too.
Yes, we need to talk to you.
- Of course, sit down.
Glass of water?
- Yes, please.
Did you fail again?
I didn't.
- Then why are you walking so weird?
Mary thinks that jerking
off means jerking it off.
Ohhh, great.
Ms. Salt, I'll get straight to the point.
- Drink up.
Yes, Ms. Salt.
First of all, I think you
are a very beautiful woman.
In the prime of your life.
And me...
- Hulst is dumping you.
Yes, so that.
But Mr. Hulst is stupid,
because he doesn't see...
how nice and...
- Over.
Done, finished. Bye!
What?
You're a licked sandwich.
I had saved myself for you, whore.
Erik, what are you doing?
Sorry, Ms. Salt.
- Guys, this is a misunderstanding.
I have nothing going on
with Mr. Hulst at all.
No?
- We're just colleagues. Nothing more.
What made you think that?
- You're his bitch.
Well, no um...
I have to do something.
Tim, will you make sure
Erik stays here?
Yes.
No one can tame me, dude!
Faggot!
Dude, what's wrong with you?
Do you still want to break up?
Whose are you?
- Yours! I'm Salty's!
What are you?
- I'm a naughty little slut.
Hey!
No, not again. Sorry, Erik.