The costumes?
- Check.
Face paint?
Wigs?
Check. I arranged everything, since
you were busy growing a moustache.
In terms of balloons I got
25 with my own piss...
fifteen with my dog's
piss, five mixed...
I filled one black balloon with piss
from someone called Toothless Tilly.
Blood for the shock
value is all covered.
It was a little hard to
arrange the blood...
but my cousin Wesseltje ran over a
deer last night, so we can use that.
A deer?
In this town?
- Yeah, at the petting zoo.
How horrible.
- Very.
First we had to get his
scooter over the fence.
Then you have to catch an animal.
Even though they're idle,
they're still wild animals.
They're agile.
- Did you hit that deer on purpose?
No! No way.
We were aiming for the old fat one.
But you have to be content with what
hits your bumper. They're packed.
Were you driving fast?
No. I wasn't.
Wesseltje was.
And fast too. He weighs 43 kilos,
so he flew over those plains.
What did Wesseltje think of it?
He was fine with it, I think.
He had to cry in the end, but that's
because his scooter broke down.
Why didn't you get the
blood from a butcher?
No way. I won't let some butcher
mess up the senior prank.
That's what I said to Wesseltje too,
as he was weeping on his scooter.
I said: there are five deer here, but
the senior prank happens only once.
Except for that we'll come back
and we do it again next year.
Just don't say that to Wesseltje.
Whatever!
Last day of classes.
You'll still need those books
for your exams, so to speak.
Whatever! Last day of classes!
Our final class,
boys and girls.
It's been a long and difficult year.
But we all worked hard for it.
I'm proud of you.
Spend the coming days well
to study for your exams, and...
- Armani, what is it?
Sir, can you close the window?
I'm speaking right now,
this is not the time.
But it's so cold here.
Are you cold? Go stand in
the corner. It's 90 degrees.
Could I take a picture with you?
That's one vile moustache, pal.
Goodbye, childhood.
Gruppe!
Achtung!
Steh auf!
Augen gerade aus!
Also.
Let's continue where we left off, ja!
Lebensraum.
Sehr gut!
Kristallnacht!
Damnit, Heydrich!
I was explaining to Harakiri that
he has to leave his sword at home...
and keep his insides inside...
and you shoot him through his skull!
Really, quit it!
Anyway, continue with your final class.
Were you teaching German?
Of course, I'm a German teacher.
You're a German teacher, but
you don't teach German.
You teach sociology.
But I just want to teach German so bad.
No, no, no. No way.
Get back to the material for the exams.
Got it? 1950s.
The Dutch political climate
after the Second World War.
Is the war over?
No, he just wants your gold.
And then Mr. Heydrich had to
talk about post World War II...
and he basically said it was tied.
- Such a nice cup of coffee.
But Mr. Hulst didn't let him lie, so...
get this, Mr. Heydrich started crying.
Big German tears.
It was amazing.
My goodness, what a nice
cup of joe. For real.
Can I get a sip? I've never had it.
- Tim, don't start.
You won't be able to stop.
I'm simply addicted.
Don't be so childish, give it to me.
Put that down, Tim.
What's she saying?
In this classroom
we only speak English.
You know, yes? Put that
down, Tim. Put it down.
Hello.
Throw it away!
Away!
Ah, yeah. Yeah.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Alright, yeah.
Hello, everybody.
My name... is thirteen years old.
My favourite hobbies is...
blue...
and yellow.
My husband...
My sincere apologies for my...
laughably simple-minded,
childlike classmate, Mrs. Wevers.
I'll throw it away forthwith.
Why is he throwing it out?
Because it's not allowed, Tim.
Hey, Tim!
You suck your modder's dick!
Almost, Armani.
It's not 'modder', it's 'mother'.
What'd he say?
You suck your mother's dick.
What does that mean?
In this classroom,
I only speak English.
Hey, Eddy!
What did Armani say to me?
I can't repeat that, Tim. My
parents don't let me cuss.
I can write it down for you.
- Yes, do that.
But I can't read braille.
Then you should ask my new
best friend Onno. He's next to me.
Hey, Onno! Onno,
what did they say about me?
Onno!
Onno can't hear you. He's deaf.
Why did you tell me to ask him?
- We always pull these kinds of pranks.
How do you even know each other?
The sauna.
Before you open this,
I need to talk to you.
It's the final day of school, and then
I might only see you at the prom.
The past few weeks have been very
special to me, and I wanted to say...
Dear Barteljaap,
I'm very proud of you, and...
it's the headwind that
makes the kite rise...
and look at how high you've risen.
I want to reward you for the
hard work and the long wait and...
the time has come.
I will... what? Comfort!
What is it?
What'd she say?
Barteljaap, I went along
with this for a while...
but there's things that I won't, can't
and am legally   not allowed to say.
That doesn't even exist!
That's physically impossible.
What's she saying?
I'm curious.
Sorry, Barteljaap,
but I can't do this.
You're such a sweet girl, Comfort.
I don't know what's happening here...
but I could cut the sexual
tension with a knife.
Well, what do I care?
I'm just happy I'm out
of the endless maze.
MAZE
Remi?
Remi, no!
I wanted to keep you out of this.
This is unacceptable.
You've got nothing to do with this.
She's only a child.
I'm not like that.
No, Remi, no!
What Comfort and I have is different.
Of course she's a sweet girl.
She's the only one who's
ever smiled to me.
And we have fun, and...
And of course she's a
beautiful girl to see...
But no! No, Remi, no!
The only reason you're so...
present, is because you've had to...
wait for 13.536 nights.
And that's a lot. A big lot.
You've waited for that long,
so surely you can add, er...
Her birthday's in June,
she's 11 years old...
2276 nights to that, right?
Alright. Will you lay low now?
Won't you ever scare me again?
Promise?
Well then.
Shall we play with the adults, then?
Do you like this one?
Open the fly, then.
Prank! Prank!
This'll make all those
years here worth it.
Listen up. First we do a final day-dump.
Then we change clothes, get the deer...
- I'm good.
I'll say goodbye to the teachers,
and then turn homeward.
Could you imagine? One question...
Do you think that I can sell the deer
to the butcher when we're done?
Tim, don't bother me with
your childish nonsense.
What is it with you?
Nature sent me a sign, Tim.
When I say Bartel, you say Jaap!
- I got a moustache.
I'm fully-grown now. You stop celebrating
leaving behind a period of your life.
Yes, but...
- I want to go forward, Tim.
And you're stopping me.
- What about the prank? And...
You should watch Bambi.
Why? I'm not a toddler.
- That's exactly what you are.
You don't even have a dream job.
How could you even say that?
You know what my dream job is.
Oh really? What is it?
Cowboypainter.
Oh, really? Then what are you?
A cowboy who paints...
or do you only paint cowboys?
- Exactly, cowboypainter.
Mr Heydrich, hi.
I understood the students
are tough on you.
No way, it's nothing.
Well, that's good news.
Then... I just wanted to say sorry.
for punching you after the match.
I don't know what you're saying.
I can't remember it.
Well....
If there's anything I can do for you...
Kein Dank. I'm very busy.
Tchüss!
Mr Heydrich, a little kindness won't hurt.
You don't have to be ashamed for it.
Benevolence always pays off in the end.
Just look at me.
Nein.
Alles ist vorbei.
Oh, Mammi!
Wo bist du?
Mein Mammi!
When I was still a little Mr Heydrich...
when I was living with...
lieber Pappi, Klaus, in Argentinien.
And mein Pappi was
a simple Bauer, a farmer.
And everything was schön.
When, suddenly...
from one day to the next...
my papa got taken away by the Jüdische
Geheimdienst and hanged in Israel.
You wouldn't know the
feeling, of course...
When your innocent Pappi...
suddenly gets taken away from
his farm, never to be seen again.
And why?
Just because he was German?
And when I found out that
all those years, you two...
lived in Pappi's basement for free...
I wanted Rache.
I mean revenge.
But not anymore.
I just want to be honest.
The world is no longer at war.
And all the people hug each other...
And you're free.
Deutschland hat verloren.
Go.
Just go, um Gottes Willen.
You can go.
No, no, we're going that way.
Bello, Tim...
piss Tim...
Hi.
Sorry.
You've got lot of balloons.
- Great, isn't it?
You only have one final day of school.
But you're failing on purpose
and do it again next year.
Why don't you just try?
You're capable of so much more.
You still have a few weeks.
I could help you.
No, no, no. I can't, Mary. I'm sorry.
I have a deal with my blood brother.
And where is he?
Alright, I'm going to cry
from my bushes. Bye.
Don't throw it at me. Seriously.
- Do you want to join?
No, I don't want to ruin my sweater.
Get over it, dude.
Alright. This has happened.
I won't react to this.
I'm better than this toddler.
Of course, go home. Go read a book.
Yes.
You know what book?
A textbook. You know why?
To study for my exams.
No! Erik, you can't!
We had a deal!
Oh, really?
I don't remember
signing anything.
Erik!
Dickhead.
Whatever! Last day of school!