[In English]
So...
Tim.
You failed another exam.
It's absolutely abysmal.
I had to give you a 2.7, and
then I'm cutting you some slack...
because you even forgot
to write down your own surname.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Do you understand
what I'm saying, Tim?
Yeah, yeah. English.
It's not looking good.
What's your grade at the moment?
Yes.
What's your grade, Tim?
Yes, I know.
[In Dutch]
What is your grade?
Oh, a three.
English, please.
Een dree.
A tree.
[In English]
A tree?
I'm a lumberjack now?
I went to the forest with my axe
and I cut down a tree for you?
Don't you mean 'a three'?
Oh, yeah, yeah. A 'free'.
A free what?
A free Africa?
I don't do anything for free.
[In Dutch]
Can't I just get a second chance?
If you ask me in English,
maybe you can.
I don't get what you're saying.
Are you mentally retarded, Tim?
Yes?
Honey, we've got the room.
We've  got the room in Groningen.
We're moving in together!
Wow. Fun, fun.
I hoped you'd be more excited.
Sorry, I had such a strange
conversation just now.
I'm still confused.
Did you get a bad grade?
I believe we didn't talk about that.
I don't know what she said.
That's okay. I'm going to help you.
Of course.
- We're in this together.
We're moving in together!
I'm going to call my parents.
She was excited.
You must've aced that test.
Well, not really...
- What was your grade?
I get the feeling I didn't do well...
but I'm not so sure.
- That is amazing news.
Why?
- I had an epiphany tonight...
and everything is clear to me now.
- What is it?
Tim, what is the worst thing in the world?
- School.
And what is the best thing?
- No school.
Exactly.
And that's why...
we are going to stay here next year.
Huh?
- It's brilliant.
It's revolutionary.
We spend the next few months
doing nothing...
because we won't pass anyway.
Summer holiday starts now.
No worries,
I'm giving Lars a wash.
But Erik, I can make it still.
Given the fact we got
two months left...
and Ms. Wevers needs
a good day to grant me a resit.
5 divided by 7 times 365 divided by 12
is 21,7 school days per month.
Statistically, someone is grumpy
five percent of the time.
Then Ms. Wevers is
0,05 times 21,7 equals...
1,085...
meaning she is grumpy for 2,17
schooldays in two months.
Let's say she has two
additional lousy days a month...
Four days in total on top of
the 2,17 lousy days, makes 6,17...
This is the corridor, once again.
Eddy.
The corridor.
Sorry, guys.
No worries.
Anyways, there are 60 days
left in total...
those contain 44 school days and
24 classes by her.
6,17 lousy days divided by 44 is...
0,14. That times 24 is 3,36 days
that she will be teaching crankily.
So 24 minus that 3,36 is 20,64
divided 24 is 0,86...
is an 86 percent chance that
if asked nicely...
She will grant me
a resit for the exam.
I got a 3,7 without studying, so
if I study I can get a 6,7 easily.
That's exactly what I need
to just pass English.
But that doesn't change
that I'm failing maths.
No chance you can get that grade up.
When did you ever get a
passing grade for maths?
Fuck it, let it go.
Don't go studying like your life
depends on it just to fail.
We will fail our exams.
We'll try again next year.
What about Mary?
- Fuck Mary.
I've been trying.
The weather is gonna be nice,
we can play soccer all day...
We can watch watch videos all day
and say we're doing homework...
although we're watching videos
because we don't have to do homework...
so we're watching videos.
- Fuck! That's too cool.
With all due respect,
your grades are laughibly bad.
There is no reason why you'd
still want to pass.
The reason is Mary who found
a place for us in Groningen.
And what about me?
I'm your very, very, very,
very, very best friend.
I'm so lonely without you.
- I'd be lonely too.
It's the only way. Mary would kill me.
Calm down, moving in
together is not that exciting.
Moving in!
We're moving in!
Tim and I are gonna moving in together!
We'll be roommates!
- Say it, now.
Who wants to see my pussy?
Alright, I'll tell her.
She should've known it from the start.
I'm a lone wolf, a rolling stone.
Yes?
What's so funny?
I can't say.
Okay.
I can say it, actually. You'll get
a surprise test next week.
Alright, but now it's not
a surprise anymore.
Since you just told us.
You're right, so it'll be today.
Danke Erik, you can stay after school.
Call that a surprise.
Thank you, Erik.
Another test I will fail.
If Mary had known, it
wouldn't have mattered.
I can't tell her now
because there's a test.
And I won't share this candy with you.
Bye.
Hey, handsome.
I'm not handsome.
Did you make some time free for me?
I won't graduate, I think.
What made you think that?
If you just try your best...
- Knock it off, my grades are terrible.
Then what will you do?
You will be all alone next year.
And I'll be in Groningen.
And Erik will be...
God knows where.
- He stays here too.
No way.
Erik can pass easily.
- He has made up his mind.
But that means...
so...
You'll stay here because of Erik.
No, it's not final yet.
You do whatever your baby does?
- You know you are my baby.
Why are you doing this?
- What else am I to do?
My grade for maths is a 3, for
English it's barely a 5.
I'd need to study for hours a day,
and I wouldn't come close.
I can finally enjoy the weather and stuff.
So stay here with your little buddy Erik.
Keep being a high schooler
until your twenties.
Can't we have a mature
conversation about this?
You're not mature, Tim.
Enjoy those last two
months of school. Bye.
Mary!
And this...
Forget about it!
Eddy.
- Sorry.
It's okay.
When you feel lonely...
sit on your hand.
Say, 15 or 20 minutes
of sitting on your hand...
you'll lose feeling, and it starts to look
white, it'll get numb...
you then close your eyes...
and start jerking off.
It's as if someone else
is doing it. Amazing.
Or sit on your dick instead...
and jerk off.
It's like jerking off someone else.
Or you could sit on your dick
and on your hand...
it's like someone is
jerking off someone else.
Or someone jerking off themselves.
Or you could sit on someone's
dick and then jerk off.
Bye.
Mondays.
What happened?
Detention with Heydrich.
- Of course.
You?
It's over.
Shit, man.
- Yeah, shit.
What shall we do? Do we go?
No, we stay.
We stay?
We stay.