The Lord was my shepherd.
And now the Lord is dead, the poor animal.
Normally I'd be very happy for the Lord...
because he would've
gone to a better place.
But apparently, everything has changed.
I don't know what to believe in anymore.
The Lord is with the Lord.
And the Lord will accept
the Lord, and in turn...
the Lord will accept the Lord as the Lord.
What are you talking about?
Well, just...
your dog is with God.
That's utter hogwash.
That's what I mean, Mr. Hulst.
Normally I'd be on my knees
when thinking of a hog.
But now?
Now there's nothing.
I mean, not nothing.
I'm still a woman, I still get wet. But...
Something has changed.
- Absolutely. I can't teach anymore.
I can no longer listen and head to...
Head. Still nothing.
Sure, a little wet.
those so-called scientist who claim
that a monkey screwed an ape...
and that we descend from that.
You could go until everything
descents from an ameba.
That's just nature, right?
- Plenty of people have an ameba's IQ...
Ans, Beertje...
Mister...
I noticed something's changed too.
Look at me. What do you see?
Of course, you see my swag. Of course.
But it's not the same, nonchalant,
dirty swag I had first.
Anyway, I know what this is about.
What we thought to be
impossible has happened.
Tim and Erik have a falling-out.
That's Satan's work.
-Oh, draught.
In the extraordinary sensitive ecosystem
that I've created for this school...
everything has to link together.
The suicide rates among
first-years has never been this high.
Everyone is sad, no one can work anymore.
Today, the final exams start.
If Tim and Erik aren't together
before the English exam...
then all students will fail.
That means the school will close.
Bring Tim and Erik together.
That is our mission.
Understood.
I thank you for your trust.
I won't let you down.
The windows shine like a mirror.
Just like Tim and Erik's
friendship will shine again.
Silence in the library, please.
That's correct.
Correct, too.
Also somewhat correct.
Mary, this is crazy.
Even without those cheat
sheets I did really well.
I'm going to pass Dutch as well.
Just one more exam, English.
If I manage to get a 4/10...
I will still graduate.
Ouch, my pussy.
That's really good, Tim.
I'm proud of you.
Erik thought he could screw
me over by abandoning me...
but this guy will pass.
I'm gonna win you back
with my intelligence.
Mary, Mary. Books scare me.
I have an artwork and
a question for you.
Who's he?
I can't believe you used to date him.
- I was sad, Tim.
And Armani made me
feel like I was special.
That when we were together, there
was nothing besides him and me.
But I quickly realized that
that wouldn't last forever.
So that tattoo is fake?
- No, just stupid.
But why did you spell it wrong?
- This is how you write 'Armani'.
You should see how
they write 'Champagne'.
You gave me a dark magic thing...
I'll get you...
Hi.
Silence in the library!
No matter how much
I like talking to you...
I'm on a mission. I've been
speaking English for three weeks.
Just three more hours to go.
I better get to work.
Hello.
Oh, sorry.
We need to help Erik.
No thanks. I want nothing to do with him.
But he's your best friend.
- And I miss him...
but he became an unreliable,
boring, humourless traitor.
It's not his fault.
It's his moustache.
What?
- I read a book in the library...
that said that a moustache
at a young age...
Wait a minute, you read a book?
You can't read, right?
No, but Onno can.
But he can't talk, right?
No, but he can write.
But you can't read that.
No, but Onno can.
Yeah...
Why doesn't Erik take the
moustache off himself?
Erik has been taken over by his moustache.
Help us, Tim. Destroy the
moustache, destroy evil.
I'm sorry. I'm choosing my school carreer.
Oh Tim...
Choosing your school carreer...
You make me wetter than
Ms. Salt on first-years camp.
How's your English?
Yes!
- Oh yeah?
Are you ready for your exam?
I can give you an exam.
Multiple choice.
First you only had this choice.
Now you're about to graduate,
you have multiple choices.
Follow me, bad boy.
DEBATE CLUB
I'm in favour, Onno is against.
What are you?
I'm by definition not in
favour or against something...
I think that currently it's very important
to look for nuance in the public debate.
Besides I'd first need to know what you're
debating before I decide on a position.
The claim is...
Deported asylum-seekers'
handicapped kids...
can use drones as euthanasia
during gay marriage.
And that's how it happpened.
While Erik was thinking, I
robbed him of his moustache.
Tim and Erik can be friends again...
and everything will be as it was.
That's amazing news, Eddy.
Here.
That's 100 euros.
A 100-euro coin.
May I see it?
No, the moustache.
O, sorry.
Wow, unheimisch.
I also shaved his other
moustache, for good measure.
What?
I had to come in?
Yes.
Thanks for coming.
And have a safe trip back.
Childish.
And, Eddy...
I'm in favour.
- Okay.
Erik is on his way to the gym hall.
The final exams are about to start.
I leaked to China that his
moustache enhances potency.
They can bust in any second now.
I spread a rumour on the deep web...
that Erik's moustache
offended the prophet.
The whole universe could implode, Eddy.
Stop! I have a brilliant idea.
My cousin, Pun Paul, is in town.
Pun Paul? Wouldn't he come back on Friday?
That's what we thought.
We know he doesn't lie.
And when he returned...
he was on a horse, and
insisted he didn't lie.
He said the horse's name is Friday...
so he returned on Friday.
He's the only one who can save us.
This'll get punny.
Punny like funny.
Who was that nice gentleman?
Erik, you must fail this exam.
Where's your moustache?
- Pun Paul just stole it.
Pun Paul?
- Yeah, Pun Paul.
He said that he moustache me a question.
must ask.
Just now I thought it was funny,
but I actually hate puns.
Yes, alright. But you
have to fail this exam.
Why?
- Tim really won't make it.
He does look very confident.
It was amazing. She drags
me into the bathroom...
she puts her dungarees up,
her big underpants off...
so I push her over and bend down...
Believe me. Or he'll be
here alone next year.
You think he'll fail?
I just had sex with Tim.
- Nice.
And I was doing dirty talk in English...
and I repeatedly yelled...
wrong hole, wrong hole.
But he doesn't get it.
At a certain point she's so horny,
her yelling gets unintelligible. Like...
It was magnificent.
Very tight though.
Anyway, I lost my virginity.
Anyway, I'm still a virgin.
I'm serious. You can't betray him.
What if he makes it and
I'm here on my own?
Erik, he...
- Mary.
We're starting. Take a seat.
Can I keep standing?
Nice.
I don't get it. He drew
a really strange thing...
with an incomprehensible text.
I've studied myself to
death and I'll graduate...
and Erik will stay here all alone.
Why did he do that?
Because I asked him to.
Because he shouldn't
abandon you next year.
But I'm not going to fail, Mary!
You ruined everything.
Erik is my best friend...
and now it's all over,
thanks to you. Thanks a lot.
I did all the exams brilliantly,
and English best of all.
I'll probably get a 10!
TWO WEEKS LATER
Yeah...
That's a 10, right?
No, that's a 10,4.
All added together.
You forgot the 0,4 in English.
Right. That's still higher than a 10.
Oh well, next year I'll have another go.
And I've got you.
Tim, I'm sorry.
I always dreamt of marrying you...
my childhood sweetheart.
and that we'd grow old together...
and one day we'd move to Morocco with a
lot of Dutch people to ruin their country.
But even though you're nice,
and cute...
and funny.
You're just too dumb for me.
No. Mary, I'm super smart.
Look, these grades don't reflect... Hey.
don't reflect how intelligent I really am.
I'm so smart.
Really, Tim?
Who am I kidding?
I have no idea what you said.
FAILED!
P.S. THAT WAS DEFINITELY CORA
THE COFFEE GIRL'S PUSSY, RIGHT?
FAILED!
WHAT THE FUCK, TIM?!
Wow, Tim.
You really ruined all of your exams.
Yeah.
- Sorry dude.
Oh, that's...
- Shit.
What?! Did you get a 0,4 in English?
I got a 1,2, but I drew a pussy.
Oh, a pussy.
What did you even do?
Yeah... I also made a...
really nasty drawing.
Anyway, we're both staying!
We're staying!
I was doing really bad for a while...
That moustache brought
me to a really dark place...
Hey guys. Do you have a pun for me?
Because I want them P-all.
Get it? P-aul?
Yeah, so anyway...
Hey guys!
It's hole baloney.
Get it?
All baloney?
Just try it yourself.
It's all baloney.
That doesn't make sense, Paul.