I lost a friend...
We all...
lost a friend.
The events at the prom last week...
are a dark stain on the history
of this beautiful school.
Of course, because of the tragic death...
that happened amongst us.
Also because we, as school...
did nothing to prevent this.
We just stood by...
and we did nothing.
How you...
through a cowardly act
of an evil individual...
got ripped from our lives.
And now...
Now it's too late.
But I learned so much from you.
I know that you would've
wanted us to remain strong.
That we continue with
this life with an open...
and candid view whilst facing the future.
Just like you always did.
You were always there.
For us.
But weren't always there for you.
The thought...
of no longer being able to
tickle you behind your ears...
is maddening.
Rest in peace...
dear Cookie.
I want to ask you all to head to
the back for coffee and cake.
And then in a minute...
the summer holiday will start for you all.
By the way, before I forget...
Next year, I will be your maths teacher.
Because, uhm. Err...
What was his name again?
No, no, no.
Small nose with that Chinese bitch.
Barteljaap?
- Right, right.
Barteljaap is dead. And, err...
For the next six weeks, you're
no longer my responsibility.
Enjoy your holiday...
and live fast and die young!
HORRORPEDO GETS WHAT HE DESERVES
Why does no one come back
after the summer break?
Us three will come back.
Why?
Well, they all graduated.
And we didn't, so we have to turn back.
There you go.
Now your backs have been turned, by me.
My dad arranged for
me to spend...
the first two years of my study
in New York, so that's fun.
Wow, fun.
- Cool!
I'm excited to go to Oxford.
Meet new people, different culture...
Just...
giving my pussy a fresh breeze.
And you, Roslin?
I'll be in the Marine Corps.
My altitude training in
the Himalayas is next week.
Oh, fun.
Coffee, disgusting.
Hey guys, I'm coming...
to say goodbye.
Wow, that coffee is hot.
I won't see you after the
break, and maybe never.
Thanks for everything, and...
I wish you the best.
Mate, what's that for?
I've never liked you,
so I won't kiss you.
Me neither.
- Than we can shake hands.
Hey Timmy.
- Hey.
Thanks for everything.
- Do you want to date me?
No.
- Please.
Please.
- No.
Tony.
You want some cake?
No, thanks. I've got Cookie.
Well..
Guys, have a nice holiday.
Good luck with, er...
Until when, actually?
Have a nice...
See you next year, Armani.
- Next year I kill you.
Whatever, plenty of time.
Summer holiday!
SIX WEEKS LATER
Holiday over.
And you're back again.
It went over quick.
And that's part of your "plan"?
Yeah, you see...
we thought...
- we thought that if we...
did nothing for the last two months,
and we had summer holiday too...
then...
-then we would have...
a 3 and a half month long break.
so that we...
would have a longer break, really.
And?
Yeah, it was... Err...
Very fun.
We kind of underestimated
that for those last two months...
we still had to go to school.
- But it was, uh...
It was fun.
- Yeah.
But now you're back here again.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
Whereas if you had studied last year,
you could've been free all year.
Some partying, playing soccer.
Some fingering.
Yeah.
- Yeah. Stupid.
Guys, aren't you smarter than this?
Don't throw away your future.
Do you want to spend your twenties
in school like that retard of an Armani?
But Mr. Hulst, you see...
This year will be easy because we've
had all classes last year already.
And last year we failed on purpose.
Why do you think we both made
a drawing on our English exam?
Tim didn't make a drawing.
Tim wrote a very long essay...
in what us teachers think
has to represent English.
We had a good laugh.
We all have it frame in our homes.
What?
Sorry, I wanted to graduate
to prove I was able to.
So...
You can't relax this year.
You have to study like crazy.
Yeah.
I'm still burnt.
- Sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Anyway, what you're really here for is...
Say....
Dick or ass?
I can't go on. I'm exhausted.
Knock it off, Tony.
Why don't you take a hit?
No way. I got sober this summer.
No, don't be weird.
Here, treat yourself.
- No, I'm sober now.
Come on.
Alright.
That was class 1C.
You can let the kids in 1D come in now.
I'm exhausted.
Eight first-year classes this year.
Is it just me, or do they
get younger every year?
No, Tim. We get old.
Listen Tim, I'm going to
help you pass this year.
We'll become big nerds.
Here it is, page 34.
Hey, guys,
Free me. Guys.
Viktor, you can get anywhere.
Gym hall?
- No, not there.
Please, please. The world is a prison.
Bye, Viktor.
Can I get some food?
Smile.
Jump through that hoop.
Guys.
I heard that pedo is dead.
Can I teach maths?
Please! Can I teach maths?
- No, Mr. Hulst does it.
Viktor, you got fired. It's over.
Listen, I'll be normal. Really.
And we've become big nerds,
so we'll go to class on time. Bye.
Oh really? Really?
I'll come back! Believe me!
Remember that I'm one of them! Hey!
Remember that I'm one of them!
Guys!
So, his net monthly
income is 12,5 thousand.
But, he has some fixed expenses.
A place for his mistress, he has
to pay at least one girl restitution...
Each weekend he sprays
champagne on hobos...
What an ugly vase.
Bye, vase.
He pays three times
alimony. Or, Mr. Hulst...
You got three ex wives, right?
No, four.
Yeah, seed has to flow, young man.
And he gets a haircut five times a month.
So if you deduct all that money...
of what he normally makes,
you're left with 120 euros.
But, he wants more.
Love.
- That's what I was getting at.
Now he meets with a cheap Romanian
hooker at a diner every Friday.
But, the next day he's at the poker
table with a penicillin shot in his nuts.
He could dine with an expensive escort...
that would mean spending
more on a drink...
but at the end of the month he needs
to have cash to throw at people.
So, the question is...
How much extra can he pay himself
for his job as maths teacher...
to keep this lifestyle going?
Assuming that he saved a lot of
money on the previous teacher.
So there is quite a big budget.
So...
The "A" is pronounced like an "E".
"E" sounds like "I".
So the "A" is "I".
No, "I" sounds like "Y".
I.
Yeah, also.
- What?
So also, eye.
Aai.
No, the word for "aai" is pet.
Hat.
The "O" stays an "O".
The "U" sounds like "you".
- Me.
You.
Yes. And the "Y" sounds like "why".
Why?
- Correct.
What?
Do yo get it now?
Nai.
I've tought so much.w
Listening, paying attention...
Being on time. That room
was empty. No one there.
It's not possible. We need a new plan.
I can't think of anything.
Luckily, I have a genius plan. Tim...
What is the most important thing on...
- Friendship.w
Exactly.
And Tim. What is...
Symbiotically dragging yourself
into someone else's misery.
That's why we need to...
do each other's tests.
It's genius.
It's revolutionary.
See...
You put your name on half your tests...
And you put my name on the other half.
If I get a 10 for every test.
Which is possible if I study hard...
then you only need to
show up to get a 1...
then at the and of the year we'll
have a 5.5 average for all our classes.
But crucially, you need to get
at least a 1 for all your tests.
So, write your name correctly.
Remember to write your name
according to the old spelling.
So Tim Pankake, with a K. Not Tim Pancake.
Pancake. No.
Pankake.
You know what this means.
We're gonna graduate.
We're bceoming adults.
I can feel it.
I'm ready for the next
stage in our friendship.
It's serious now.
We're such special boys.
It's over, Emily!
It's me again, Tim.
It's okay, Eddy.
Are you Tim and Erik?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
You urgently need to see Mr. Heydrich.
He said he has a special task for you.
You need to look after a panda.
Responsibility.
You know what'd be cool?
If we'd build a hut that we
could piss in during recess.
Yeah! And we'd call it: the pisshut.
Even thinking of it makes me want to pee.